gm
this beautiful
lets go
Subtitles - MitchSirco
For a better closed captions experience, watch them on Desktop :3
------------------------------------------------
When I'm on my own
I hear your call
I feel the sun and the sky's my home
If you find me now
We′ll have it all
Yeah I have it all
When you're holding on
I've been waiting for something
I think you′re something
Yeah I have it all
When you're holding on
I've been waiting for something
I know you′re something
Yeah, I
------------------------------------------------
I'm running out
I'm running out of time to save my soul
From falling out and off the edge again, now
I'm running out
Running through the seconds in my chest
But I keep waiting for the time I can
Everywhere I look it's counting
​       D​
​      DO​
​     DOO​
​    DOOO​
​   DOOOO​
​  DOOOOO​
​ DOOOOOO​
​DOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOo​
​OOOOOOoo​
​OOOOOooo​
​OOOOoooo​
​OOOooooo​
​OOoooooo​
​Oooooooo​
​oooooooo​
They forgave my heart
​oooooooᵒ​
​ooooooᵒᵒ​
​oooooᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooooᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
Forgave you in my soul
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʷ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʷⁿ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʷⁿ ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒʷⁿ  ​
​ᵒᵒᵒʷⁿ   ​
​ᵒᵒʷⁿ    ​
​ᵒʷⁿ     ​
​ʷⁿ      ​
​ⁿ      ​​
​       o​
​      oo​
​     ooo​
​    oooo​
​   ooooo​
​  oooooo​
​ ooooooo​
​oooooooo​
Would you stay around
​oooooooO​
​ooooooOO​
​oooooOOO​
​ooooOOOO​
​oooOOOOO​
​ooOOOOOO​
​oOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOo​
​OOOOOOoo​
​OOOOOooo​
​OOOOoooo​
Or just let me go
​OOOooooo​
​OOoooooo​
​Oooooooo​
​oooooooo​
​oooooooh​
​ooooooh ​
​oooooh  ​
​ooooh   ​
​oooh    ​
​ooh     ​
​oh     ​​
​       O​
​      OO​
​     OOO​
​    OOOO​
​   OOOOO​
​  OOOOOO​
​ OOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOo​
​OOOOOOoo​
​OOOOOooo​
​OOOOoooo​
​OOOooooo​
​OOoooooo​
If you find me now
​Oooooooo​
​oooooooo​
​oooooooᵒ​
​ooooooᵒᵒ​
​oooooᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooooᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
We'll have it
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ  ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ   ​
​ᵒᵒᵒʰ    ​
​ᵒᵒʰ     ​
​ᵒʰ      ​
​           a​
​          aa​
​         aaa​
​        aaaa​
​       o​
​       aaaaa​
​      oo​
​      aaaaaa​
​     ooo​
​     aaaaaaa​
​    oooo​
​    aaaaaaaa​
​   ooooo​
​   aaaaaaaaa​
​  oooooo​
​  aaaaaaaaaa​
​ ooooooo​
​ aaaaaaaaaaa​
​oooooooo​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​oooooooO​
​ooooooOO​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​oooooOOO​
​ooooOOOO​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​oooOOOOO​
​ooOOOOOO​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​oOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOO​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaaaaaA​
​OOOOOOOO​
​aaaaaaaaaaAA​
​aaaaaaaaaAAA​
​OOOOOOOO​
​aaaaaaaaAAAA​
​aaaaaaaAAAAA​
​OOOOOOOO​
​aaaaaaAAAAAa​
​aaaaaAAAAAaa​
​OOOOOOOO​
​aaaaAAAAAaaa​
​OOOOOOOo​
​aaaAAAAAaaaa​
​OOOOOOoo​
​aaAAAAAaaaaa​
​OOOOOooo​
​OOOOoooo​
​aAAAAAaaaaaa​
​OOOooooo​
​AAAAAaaaaaaa​
​OOoooooo​
​AAAAaaaaaaaa​
​Oooooooo​
​AAAaaaaaaaaa​
​oooooooo​
​AAaaaaaaaaaa​
​Aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​oooooooo​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaaaaal​
​oooooooh​
​aaaaaaaaaall​
​ooooooh ​
​aaaaaaaaall ​
​oooooh  ​
​aaaaaaaall  ​
​ooooh   ​
​aaaaaaall   ​
​oooh    ​
​aaaaaall   ​​
​ooh    ​​
​           O​
​          OO​
​         OOO​
​        OOOO​
​       OOOOO​
​      OOOOOO​
​     OOOOOOO​
​    OOOOOOOO​
​   OOOOOOOOO​
​  OOOOOOOOOO​
​ OOOOOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOOOOOO​
​OOOOOOOOOOOo​
​OOOOOOOOOOoo​
​OOOOOOOOOooo​
​OOOOOOOOoooo​
​OOOOOOOooooo​
​OOOOOOoooooo​
​OOOOOooooooo​
​OOOOoooooooo​
​OOOooooooooo​
​OOoooooooooo​
​Oooooooooooo​
​oooooooooooo​
​oooooooooooᵒ​
​ooooooooooᵒᵒ​
​oooooooooᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooooooooᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oooooooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooooooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oooooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ooᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​oᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ  ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ   ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ    ​
​ᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒᵒʰ    ​​
------------------------------------------------
How do I wake up and find you?
How do I know when you're there?
I need more than a whole body
I just want someone to care
And I swear
That I won't
Be afraid to choose
'Cause I want
You to know
I'd runaway with you
------------------------------------------------
Yeah, I'd runaway with you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
From the cradle to the urn
They tried to tell me exercise my patience, wait my turn
Wherever you go
Fake concern, when these pagans finna learn? Court adjourned
Paradigm shift,
my people 'bout to watch it burn
Yeah, I'd runaway-
Man are renegade
(Like a renegade)
Vagrant to the core
Pollution at its peak,
Yeah, I'd runaway-
watch as nature settles scores
Extinction level twenty,
fuck a penny for your thoughts
For the many, not the few, one-
I'd runaway-
I'd runaway with you
Yeah, yeah
Love and care the only option
New world order,
vice law the fuckin' problem
See, we can be the change,
evolution is solution
Greed, power, money, nothing more than an illusion
Delusion took its toll,
banks made the bed
Balance brought the shetty,
severed lay the head
Politics ate itself,
the people came to live
We're looking to the future like something's gotta give
(Yeah)
People power
The warehouse
(Need to)
(Hard to)
The warehouse
(Take it away now)
Like a renegade
(Running your mouth out)
(Take it away now)
------------------------------------------------
People power
Inhale
Breathe with me
Breathe the pressure
Come play my game, I′ll test ya
Psychosomatic, addict, insane
Breathe the pressure
Come play my game, I′ll test ya
Psycho- Psychosomatic, addict, insane
Come play my game
Inhale, inhale
You′re the victim
Come play my game
Exhale, exhale, exhale
Slide past the point I'm making
The words ain't of use to you
I'm watching the cold front breaking
You want victory over truth
But the truth is I never did like you
Not even just one touch
Come play my game
You don't believe in nothing
Don't you pretend too much?
Exhale, exhale, exhale
(Fall In, Fall Out)
Nobodies baby and that’s ok with me
I cut the chord to your memories
Thought it be harder but ya make it easy
When you call, I’m on a roll, let you go
I’m not devoted to you
Not ever after but I'm happy to leave
Keys on the floor, I burned your favourite T
Who's coming after you, is better for me
When you call, I’m on a roll, let you go
I’m not devoted to you
Fall In, Fall Out
I'm not devoted-
I'm not devoted to you
Fall In, Fall Out
I'm not devoted- voted-
I'm not devoted to you
But You keep telling me
All I need
Can’t you see, I’m not dеvoted to you
But You keep telling me
(your love is like)
All I need
(but I be like)
Can’t you see, I’m not dеvoted to you
I'm not devoted to you
Fall In, Fall Out
I'm not devoted-
I'm not devoted to you
Fall In, Fall Out
I'm not devoted- voted-
I'm not devoted to you
Fall In, Fall Out
I'm not devoted-
I'm not devoted to you
Fall In, Fall Out
I'm not devoted- voted-
Fall In, Fall Out-
Baby, can you tell me
What's going on?
Baby
Whip it
-y
Baby
What's going on?
Juilett
-y
Baby
Baby, can you tell me
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
What's going on?
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Baby, can you see?
Feelin' like a polar bear burnin'
What are we gonna do?
What's going- go- going on?
Baby, can you tell me
I'm that fake smile gleamin'
Yeah, I'm the lie that you choose to believe in
What's going on?
Baby, can you see?
Guess the truth kinda lost all meanin'
And I'm enjoying the view
What's going- go- going on?
Well I've been a lovin' lover
I've been a trusting brother
I'm taking my time to recover
And pickin' it up when I'm better
Oh, there's so much to see in a lifetime
So why does it feel like it flies by?
She's staring me down with the bright eyes
Don't threaten me with a good time
(Don't threaten me with a good time)
(-na na na na)
(Na na-na-na na na na na)
Na na-na-na na na na na
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Na na-na-na na na na na
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Feelin' like a polar bear burnin'
What are we gonna do?
I'm that fake smile gleamin'
Yeah, I'm the lie that you choose to believe in
Guess the truth kinda lost all meanin'
And I'm enjoying the view
👍
------------------------------------------------
Wooohoooeuh
WOOH
Born slippy, so look busy
Young scumbag got the keys to the city
I'm knee jerking, black coffee slurping
We're all screwed up but the world's still turnin'
I hug my demons, I fistbump Jesus
I thank Poseidon for a sweet surf season
When I arrive it won't be pretty
From Moscow to the great Mississippi
So
They hear the bass and they say woah
I reckon in 21 seconds
I’m about to blow this thing straight to the heavens
And then they get down on the floor
They hear the bass and they say woah
Still stressin’, Still second guessing
Paid my price but learnt no lesson
And then they get down on the floor
They hear the bass and they say-
So cold, my heavyweight soul
So weighed down by the things that I know
They hear the bass and they say-
All told I got too bold, Heart of Gold?
They hear the bass and they say whoa
No, I do it like that
They hear the bass and they say woah
Like that
And then they get down on the floor
I do it like that
They hear the bass and they say woah
Like that
And then they get down on the floor
(Oh yeah)
Like that
They hear the bass and they say woah
And then they get down on the floor
I do it like that
They hear the bass and they say woah
Like that
And then they get down on the floor
(Oh yeah)
------------------------------------------------
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
They hear the bass and they say woah
-floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
And then they get down on the floor
Dance floor, shake your body
They hear the bass and they say woah
And then they get down on the-
Like the last, like the last
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
Dance- dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
Dance- dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, time, time
We go back
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
Dance- dance floor, shake your body like the last time
We go back
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
Dance- dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Back with a track called "DRIVER"
Like the last time, time, time
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
Dance- dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, like the last time
Dance- dance floor, shake your body like the last time
Like the last time, time, time
------------------------------------------------
We set it off
Style to dangerous,
rhyms to murderous
Beat to treacherous
you can't get with this
We set it off and you scramble like you under attack
But dont run that booming sound is just a banging track
Camo krooked Jeru do more damage than a razor back
To where shit hurts
Space age forget the glock and cock the laser back
No, let 'em circle
Scientifical madness reppin' stellar weapon carbon black
So be alarmed we droppin' bombs not fiction but fact
I swing the mic and chop it down like a lumberjack
We about to blow it up so where my people at
People at
None other than the illest
Illest
🪑?
We set it off
WE SET IT OFF
❌ 🪑
None other than the illest
Illest
*Yah*
Solo Killa
Killa
None other than the illest
but what do I know
Illest
You take no bullet for me
But I know, and I still care
Illest
We set it off
I take you with me wherever I go
I keep you company, but what do I know
You take no bullet for me
But I know, and I still care
I can't find a way to get you out of my mind
When I think of you, it's like the planets and the stars align
I can't find a way to get you out of my head
So hold me close and wrap me in your arms instead
You take no Bullet for me
I can't find a way to get you out of my mind
When I think of you, the planets and the stars align
I can't find a way to get you out of my head
So hold me close and wrap me in your arms instead
------------------------------------------------
Darling you gave me an omen to save me
You don't mind I'm all in
I'm taking I know you back when
Always imagine if I told you I love you
Don't say you don't think about me
I told you I'm finding, I'm finding
I love you, I need you, we're blinding
Your blind
We're blinding
-normal kind of love with you
Come with me
‘Cause we’re never going back again
We’re gonna tear it down and start again
Come with me
‘Cause we’re never going back again
Comе with me ‘cause you’re all I need
We’re gonna tear it all down down and start again
I'm looking up to the sky for a place to go
You got me reaching up for higher ground
I’m gonna take my chances on a place unknown
You got me reaching up for higher ground
I won't let it die
I can feel you when you're not around
When the night gets cold
I won't, I won't, I won't, I won't, I won't be alone
We won't be alone
(We won't, we won't)
(We won't be alone)
(We are alone)
I'm told if we could work this out
They'd lay low
And I'm cold, this fortune's running out
We stay tall
​           O​
​          Oo​
​         Ooo​
​        Oooo​
​       Ooooo​
​      Oooooo​
​     Ooooooo​
​    Oooooooo​
​   Ooooooooo​
​  Oooooooooo​
​ Ooooooooooo​
​Oooooooooooh​
​oooooooooohh​
​ooooooooohh ​
​oooooooohh  ​
​ooooooohh   ​
​oooooohh    ​
​ooooohh     ​
​oooohh      ​
​ooohh       ​
​oohh        ​
​ohh         ​
​hh         ​​
​h          ​​
If you could change our minds
Half blind in light
When I know you're kind
(Half blind in light)
​           O​
​          Oo​
​         Ooo​
​        Oooo​
​       Ooooo​
​      Oooooo​
​     Ooooooo​
​    Oooooooo​
​   Ooooooooo​
​  Oooooooooo​
​ Ooooooooooo​
​Oooooooooooh​
​oooooooooohh​
​ooooooooohh ​
​oooooooohh  ​
​ooooooohh   ​
​oooooohh    ​
​ooooohh     ​
​oooohh      ​
​ooohh       ​
​oohh        ​
​ohh         ​
​hh         ​​
​h          ​​
If you could change our minds
Half blind in light
When I know you're kind
(Half blind in light)
I'm told if we could work this out
They'd lay low
And I'm cold, this fortune's running out
We stay tall
​           O​
​          Oo​
​         Ooo​
​        Oooo​
​       Ooooo​
​      Oooooo​
​     Ooooooo​
​    Oooooooo​
​   Ooooooooo​
​  Oooooooooo​
​ Ooooooooooo​
​Oooooooooooh​
​oooooooooohh​
​ooooooooohh ​
​oooooooohh  ​
​ooooooohh   ​
​oooooohh    ​
​ooooohh     ​
​oooohh      ​
​ooohh       ​
​oohh        ​
​ohh         ​
​hh         ​​
​h          ​​
If you could change our minds
Half blind in light
When I know you're kind
(Half blind in light)
Our love
Storming in my mind
Of lightning and fire and thunder
Will you still be there for me?
Say what you want
So say what you want
(Say what you want)
Say what you want
I'm gonna make this easy for you
Don't bother saying that you want it to be
I'm tired of playing the victim of love
No longer forcing what your eyes never see
So say what you want
Break down, we're alive
Are we running in circles, running around?
Break down, chase the light
We're all limboed on the go
Oh, running for my life
Oh, feel the light
(Feel the light)
RUNNING HIGH,
running low,
Running for my life
Oh,
running wild,
running for my life
Oh,
oh,
running wild,
running for my life
(Running for my life)
I remember when the bartender said it's on the house
You make me wanna fall in love
The weather felt better
When we were in it together
Oh I miss the way we used to talk about nothing
I hate to say I should've seen it coming
Last summer, everything was easy
(Easy)
We had it all, didn't we, baby?
No wonder, you couldn't keep me
(Keep me)
It got harder than you thought it would be
You stopped lovin' mе on the dark nights
(Dark nights)
Now you won't kiss me in the sunlight
Last summеr, I knew you'd leave me
(Leave me)
'Cause lovin' me isn't easy
If you wanted to talk, you would have texted
If I wanted to stop, I woulda let it go
But I get it,
it's alright
'Cause I can't keep my shit together
Say "Fuck it," yeah, can't debate that
Don't want shit to get better
'Cause it'd make me forget it all and I hate that
Last summer, everything was easy
(Easy)
We had it all, didn't we, baby?
No wonder, you couldn't keep me
(Keep me)
It got harder than you thought it would be
You stopped lovin' mе on the dark nights
(Dark nights)
Now you won't kiss me in the sunlight
Last summеr, I knew you'd leave me
(Leave me)
'Cause lovin' me isn't easy
Last summer, everything was easy
(Easy)
We had it all, didn't we, baby?
No wonder, you couldn't keep me
(Keep me)
It got harder than you thought it would be
You stopped lovin' mе on the dark nights
(Dark nights)
Now you won't kiss me in the sunlight
Last summеr, I knew you'd leave me
(Leave me)
'Cause lovin' me isn't easy
People, put your hands up in the air, I know you like it
Don't you fight it, I can see you're high and all excited
Flying through the night, we going up, better hold tight it
Go, go, go, go
Now we got the starline and the g-tha to desire
Let me see you jump up, come on, with me, let's go higher
Climbin' up the speakers, we gon' set this place on fire
Go, go, go
(I know you can't get enough of my sound)
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me mashin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me blaggin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
(I know you can't get enough of my sound)
(You keep)
runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin'
Away, away, away, boy
(You keep)
runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin'
Away, away, away
(You keep)
runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin'
Away, away, away, boy
(You keep)
runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin' and you're runnin'
Away, away, away
(Go, go, go)
------------------------------------------------
Craving that part of me
Touch of an angel
I drown in dependency
Bringing me close to giving in
My eyes linger
Visions of what could be
See my own creation
Can't fuck with me
Sweet poison
Numbing my brain
Walls breathing
Whispering
Fixated
Changing my ways
It's getting too much
I need a break
Keep feeling like I need it
My thoughts are 'ceiving
------------------------------------------------
My thoughts are deceiving
*Static*
Your Super Shotgun is nearby.
A relic from your past -
The Priests have kept it hidden from you in this remote location.
A
A̸
A̸̅
Ạ̸̅
Ạ̸̯̅
Ạ̸̯̅A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸
Ạ̸̯̅A̸͌
Ạ̸̯̅A̸͌̀
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀A̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴͝
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖͝
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAA̸
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎A̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̚
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̍
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̍̐
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAA
AA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͘
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAA
A̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉͘
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̓
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̓͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̓͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̅
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝A
AÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̋
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝A
AÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̐
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̾
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̾̓
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̾̓
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫
͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAA
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAA̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕A
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕A̶
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕A̶̾
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕A̶̾̃
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕A̶̾̃ͅ
Ạ̸̯̅A̸̤͌̀Á̶̝̙͛AAAAA̴̖̖͝AAÀ̸̫͎Ả̶̭̚A̵̝̍̐A̵͉̞͘A̷̤̗̓͛A̴̲̅AAAAA̴̖͓͛A̵̠̋A̶̰̐A̴̟̰̾̓AAAÄ̶͕A̶̢̾̃ͅH
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               The l​l
l​l                                      The Incident l​l
l​l                                   The Incident is l​l
l​l                          The Incident is reported l​l
l​l                     The Incident is reported last l​l
l​l              The Incident is reported last night, l​l
l​l        The Incident is reported last night, after l​l
l​l e Incident is reported last night, after multiple l​l
l​l ent is reported last night, after multiple people l​l
l​l s reported last night, after multiple people were l​l
l​l rted last night, after multiple people were found l​l
l​l last night, after multiple people were found dead l​l
l​l ght, after multiple people were found dead inside l​l
l​l t, after multiple people were found dead inside a l​l
l​l ltiple people were found dead inside a conference l​l
l​l e people were found dead inside a conference room l​l
l​l eople were found dead inside a conference room of l​l
l​l e were found dead inside a conference room of the l​l
l​l nd dead inside a conference room of the Hirobusha l​l
l​l ad inside a conference room of the Hirobusha corp l​l
l​l e a conference room of the Hirobusha corp complex l​l
l​l  conference room of the Hirobusha corp complex in l​l
l​l ce room of the Hirobusha corp complex in hamburg. l​l
l​l  the Hirobusha corp complex in hamburg.           l​l
l​l usha corp complex in hamburg.                     l​l
l​l complex in hamburg.                               l​l
l​l ex in hamburg.                               They l​l
l​l amburg.                               They appear l​l
l​l urg.                               They appear to l​l
l​l                                They appear to all l​l
l​l                           They appear to all show l​l
l​l                     They appear to all show signs l​l
l​l                  They appear to all show signs of l​l
l​l          They appear to all show signs of rampant l​l
l​l They appear to all show signs of rampant mutation l​l
l​l  appear to all show signs of rampant mutation and l​l
l​l all show signs of rampant mutation and bitemarks. l​l
l​l igns of rampant mutation and bitemarks.           l​l
l​l mpant mutation and bitemarks.                     l​l
l​l tion and bitemarks.                               l​l
l​l itemarks.                               Officials l​l
l​l rks.                               Officials deny l​l
l​l                                Officials deny any l​l
l​l                     Officials deny any connection l​l
l​l                  Officials deny any connection to l​l
l​l        Officials deny any connection to Hirobusha l​l
l​l  Officials deny any connection to Hirobusha corp: l​l
l​l ials deny any connection to Hirobusha corp: Their l​l
l​l eny any connection to Hirobusha corp: Their brand l​l
l​l any connection to Hirobusha corp: Their brand new l​l
l​l nection to Hirobusha corp: Their brand new neural l​l
l​l  Hirobusha corp: Their brand new neural implants, l​l
l​l  corp: Their brand new neural implants,           l​l
l​l  Their brand new neural implants,           which l​l
l​l ir brand new neural implants,           which are l​l
l​l ew neural implants,           which are currently l​l
l​l ral implants,           which are currently under l​l
l​l           which are currently under investigation l​l
l​l       which are currently under investigation for l​l
l​l hich are currently under investigation for posing l​l
l​l are currently under investigation for posing risk l​l
l​l  currently under investigation for posing risk to l​l
l​l tly under investigation for posing risk to public l​l
l​l er investigation for posing risk to public health l​l
l​l estigation for posing risk to public health after l​l
l​l on for posing risk to public health after showing l​l
l​l r posing risk to public health after showing many l​l
l​l risk to public health after showing many defects. l​l
l​l blic health after showing many defects.           l​l
l​l h after showing many defects.                     l​l
l​l ter showing many defects.                     The l​l
l​l ing many defects.                     The victims l​l
l​l any defects.                     The victims seem l​l
l​l  defects.                     The victims seem to l​l
l​l cts.                     The victims seem to have l​l
l​l                     The victims seem to have lost l​l
l​l               The victims seem to have lost their l​l
l​l         The victims seem to have lost their minds l​l
l​l   The victims seem to have lost their minds after l​l
l​l victims seem to have lost their minds after their l​l
l​l seem to have lost their minds after their devices l​l
l​l ost their minds after their devices malfunctioned l​l
l​l their minds after their devices malfunctioned and l​l
l​l  minds after their devices malfunctioned and sent l​l
l​l s after their devices malfunctioned and sent them l​l
l​l er their devices malfunctioned and sent them into l​l
l​l  their devices malfunctioned and sent them into a l​l
l​l devices malfunctioned and sent them into a frenzy l​l
l​l malfunctioned and sent them into a frenzy.        l​l
l​l ned and sent them into a frenzy.                  l​l
l​l nt them into a frenzy.                            l​l
l​l to a frenzy.                                   It l​l
l​l                                           It also l​l
l​l                              It also destabilized l​l
l​l                        It also destabilized their l​l
l​l                It also destabilized their genetic l​l
l​l           It also destabilized their genetic code l​l
l​l It also destabilized their genetic code promoting l​l
l​l o destabilized their genetic code promoting rapid l​l
l​l tabilized their genetic code promoting rapid cell l​l
l​l ed their genetic code promoting rapid cell growth l​l
l​l heir genetic code promoting rapid cell growth all l​l
l​l c code promoting rapid cell growth all throughout l​l
l​l  promoting rapid cell growth all throughout their l​l
l​l ng rapid cell growth all throughout their bodies. l​l
l​l ell growth all throughout their bodies.           l​l
l​l  all throughout their bodies.                     l​l
l​l ghout their bodies.                               l​l
l​l t their bodies.                               How l​l
l​l ir bodies.                               How this l​l
l​l es.                               How this device l​l
l​l                              How this device ever l​l
l​l                          How this device ever got l​l
l​l                 How this device ever got approved l​l
l​l              How this device ever got approved by l​l
l​l          How this device ever got approved by the l​l
l​l      How this device ever got approved by the FDA l​l
l​l   How this device ever got approved by the FDA is l​l
l​l this device ever got approved by the FDA is still l​l
l​l is device ever got approved by the FDA is still a l​l
l​l e ever got approved by the FDA is still a mystery l​l
l​l ver got approved by the FDA is still a mystery as l​l
l​l ot approved by the FDA is still a mystery as this l​l
l​l approved by the FDA is still a mystery as this is l​l
l​l proved by the FDA is still a mystery as this is a l​l
l​l d by the FDA is still a mystery as this is a very l​l
l​l DA is still a mystery as this is a very dangerous l​l
l​l  mystery as this is a very dangerous combination. l​l
l​l s this is a very dangerous combination.           l​l
l​l a very dangerous combination.                     l​l
l​l gerous combination.                               l​l
l​l bination.                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                               Com l​l
l​l                                           Combina l​l
l​l                                       Combination l​l
l​l                               Combination         l​l
l​l                       Combination                 l​l
l​l               Combination                         l​l
l​l       Combination                                 l​l
l​l mbination                                         l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
l​l                                            Combin l​l
l​l                                     Combination   l​l
l​l                           Combination             l​l
l​l                    Combination                    l​l
l​l             Combination                           l​l
l​l      Combination                                  l​l
l​l bination                                          l​l
l​l on                                                l​l
l​l                                                   l​l
She got that stealth glance, half smile
Black lace thigh highs
A voice that lulls me to sleep
She buttons up her jacket
Sweeps her hair to the back
I wonder what’s not for me to see
She lays a hand on my head
And I melt to my knees
A burning blush growing on my cheeks
As I glance to the side
She keeps her eyes on me
And it doesn’t take much to see
I've fallen in deep
We're in this, we're there
We feel it in the air
We blowin' up the floor like we don't have a fuckin' care
No stopping this rush
We'll never get enough
We carry on the party with the river coming up
We're moving, we're free, come join the revelry
Cause God is just a DJ preaching solidarity
Together as one, we've only just begun
We're in our fucking element, let's leave until the sun
Another long night, another sunrise
Another white line
I'm the Alpha, Omega, beginning, the end
A light in the darkness, salvation, condemned
Follow me, I'll lead you, I'll show the way
Surrender your soul, submit, obey
Follow me, your master, VR, AI
I'm smarter, I'm faster, I curate your life
Follow me, resistance is futile, my friend
We're in this together until the bitter end
On TikTok, on YouTube, on Discord, on Twitch
Get onto my platform, come on, make the switch
Follow me to glory, on Insta, my story
Follow me on everything or you'll bе FUCKING sorry
Follow me, your master, VR, AI
I'm smarter, I'm faster, I curate your life
Follow me, resistance is futile, my friend
We're in this together until the bitter end
Follow me
Feel something squirming
And I want out
Of this place, of this nothing
Something else to think about
Not a night in your rosebed
Not the evening rain
Not your warmth, not your memory
Not here again
No more forever
Oh baby, that was quite a punch
Could somebody check my pulse?
It's been a minute since I tasted blood
I forgot how good this was
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
Can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me BACK
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done thinking through it!
'Cause I got
Bruises
Doing something stupid
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
You can bet your life on that
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BA
Somebody better hold me BAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAACK
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done thinking through it!
'Cause I got
Bruises
Doing something stupid
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
Can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
Run for your fucking life
Warning, you’re my Nemesis
Warning
Oh baby, that was quite a punch
Could somebody check my pulse?
It's been a minute since I tasted blood
I forgot how good this was
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
Can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BA
Somebody better hold me BAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done thinking through it!
'Cause I got
Bruises
Doing something stupid
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
You can bet your life on that
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAAAAAAAACK
Oh
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAACK
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done thinking through it!
'Cause I got
Bruises
Doing something stupid
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
You can bet your life on that
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAACK
Oh
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAAAACK
------------------------------------------------
If time is all we have
I want to spend it right
No fear of what's to come
Just hold me close tonight
Give me a hole to fall through
A hidden door to something more
If we get one chance to live this life
Why are we still killing time?
killing
time
Why are we still killing time?
killing
time
Why are we still killing time?
killing time
Why are we-
Why are we- e- e- e- e- e-
Why are we still killing time?
time 🕛
time 🕒
time 🕕
time 🕘
time 🕛
time 🕑
time 🕓
time 🕕
time 🕗
time 🕙
time 🕛
time 🕑
time 🕓
time 🕕
time 🕗
time 🕙
time 🕛
time 🕑
time 🕓
time 🕕
time 🕗
time 🕛
time 🕑
time 🕓
time 🕕
time 🕗
time 🕙
time 🕛
time 🕑
time 🕓
time 🕕
time 🕗
time 🕙
So hit me with the rumors
Tell me how to feel,
tell me how to age
A billion users
Weaponized boredom,
idle change
We don't wanna feel useless
We just wanna get by and enjoy the day
'Cause, honestly, the truth is
No one's enjoying this anyway
It might be too much to compete with
time 🕛
time 🕒
But there's something underneath this
time 🕖
And I don't need to know the reasons
time 🕛
time 🕒
time 🕖
It ain't hard to feel the feeling
We've been choked to keep from screaming
time 🕛
time 🕒
We've been dosed into believing
time 🕖
Been eroded by the seasons
time 🕛
time 🕒
But we're human in the evening
time 🕖
Take
it
aw-
away
now
Take
it
aw-
away
now
Run-
Running
your
mouth
out
Take
it
aw-
away
now
(Oh, oh-oh, oh, oh-oh, whoa, whoa)
(whoa)
(ha ha)
Take
it
aw-
away
Take it away now
Running your mouth out
Take
it
aw-
away
-away now
Take it away now
Running your mouth out
(too much to compete with)
(But there's something underneath it)
(And I don't need to know the reasons)
(It ain't hard to feel the feeling)
🐦
🐦‍⬛
​       O​
​      Oh​
​     Oh​h
​    Ohhh​
​   Ohhh ​
​  Ohhh O​
​ Ohhh Oo​
​Ohhh Ooo​
​hhh Oooh​
​hh Ooohh​
​h Ooohh​h
​h Ooohhh​
​ Ooohhhh​
​Ooohhhhh​
​oohhhhhh​
​ohhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhhh​
I
ex-
expect
to
see
the
beau-
beauty
where
I
​       C​
​      CA​
​     CAA​
​    CAAA​
​   CAAAA​
​  CAAAAA​
​ CAAAAAA​
​CAAAAAAA​
​AAAAAAAA​
​AAAAAAAa​
​AAAAAAaa​
​AAAAAaaa​
​AAAAaaaa​
​AAAaaaaa​
​AAaaaaaa​
​Aaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaᵃ​
​aaaaaaᵃᵃ​
​aaaaaᵃᵃᵃ​
​aaaaᵃᵃᵃᵃ​
​aaaᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃ​
​aaᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃ​
​aᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
But
​       O​
​      Oh​
​     Ohh​
​    Ohhh​
​   Ohhhh​
​  Ohhhhh​
​ Ohhhhh-​
​Ohhhhh-O​
​hhhhh-Oh​
​hhhh-Ohh​
​hhh-Ohhh​
​hh-Ohhhh​
​h-Ohhhhh​
​-Ohhhhhh​
​Ohhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhh-​
​hhhhhh-O​
​hhhhh-Oh​
​hhhh-Oh-​
​hhh-Oh-O​
​hh-Oh-Oh​
​h-Oh-Oh-​
​-Oh-Oh-O​
​Oh-Oh-Oh​
​h-Oh-Ohh​
​-Oh-Ohhh​
​Oh-Ohhhh​
​h-Ohhhhh​
​-Ohhhhhh​
​Ohhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhh ​
​hhhhhh  ​
​hhhhh   ​
​hhhh    ​
​hhh     ​
perspective keeps on slipping through my
​       H​
​      HA​
​     HAA​
​    HAAA​
​   HAAAA​
​  HAAAAA​
​ HAAAAAA​
​HAAAAAAA​
​AAAAAAAA​
​AAAAAAAa​
​AAAAAAaa​
​AAAAAaaa​
​AAAAaaaa​
​AAAaaaaa​
​AAaaaaaa​
​Aaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaan​
​aaaaaann​
​aaaaannn​
​aaaannnn​
​aaannnnd​
​aannnndd​
​annnnddd​
​nnnnddds​
​nnnddds ​
​nnddds  ​
​nddds   ​
🐦
Its all just
too
much
to
com-
compete
with
Guess
that's
some-
something
I
should
deal
with
I've
been
caught
up
in
my
feel-
feelings
And
can't
seem
to
see
the
rea-
reason
We've
been
choked
to
keep
from
scream-
screaming
We've
been
dosed
in-
into
be-
belie-
believing
Been
er-
erod-
eroded
by
the
sea-
seasons
But we're human in the evening
So take it
aw-
away
now
Take
it
aw-
away
now
Run-
Running
your
mouth
out
Take
it
aw-
away
now
What
do
we
now?
What
do
we
now?
Take
it
aw-
away
now
Take
it
aw-
away
This could be good enough for us
​       O​
​      Oh​
​     Ohh​
​    Ohh ​
​   Ohh O​
​  Ohh Oo​
​ Ohh Ooo​
​Ohh Oooh​
​hh Ooohh​
​h Ooohhh​
​ Ooohhhh​
​Ooohhhhh​
​oohhhhhh​
​ohhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhhh​
I
expect
to
see
the
beauty
where
I
​       C​
​      CA​
​     CAA​
​    CAAA​
​   CAAAA​
​  CAAAAA​
​ CAAAAAA​
​CAAAAAAA​
​AAAAAAAA​
​AAAAAAAa​
​AAAAAAaa​
​AAAAAaaa​
​AAAAaaaa​
This could be good enough for us
​AAAaaaaa​
​AAaaaaaa​
​Aaaaaaaa​
This could be good enough for us
​aaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaᵃ​
​aaaaaaᵃᵃ​
​aaaaaᵃᵃᵃ​
​aaaaᵃᵃᵃᵃ​
​aaaᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃ​
This could be good enough for us
​aaᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃ​
​aᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
This could be good enough for us
​ᵃᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
​ᵃⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿⁿ​
But
​       O​
​      Oh​
​     Ohh​
​    Ohhh​
​   Ohhhh​
​  Ohhhhh​
​ Ohhhhh-​
​Ohhhhh-O​
​hhhhh-Oh​
​hhhh-Ohh​
​hhh-Ohhh​
​hh-Ohhhh​
​h-Ohhhhh​
​-Ohhhhhh​
​Ohhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhh-​
​hhhhhh-O​
​hhhhh-Oh​
​hhhh-Oh-​
​hhh-Oh-O​
​hh-Oh-Oh​
​h-Oh-Oh-​
​-Oh-Oh-O​
​Oh-Oh-Oh​
​h-Oh-Ohh​
​-Oh-Ohhh​
​Oh-Ohhhh​
​h-Ohhhhh​
​-Ohhhhhh​
​Ohhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhhh​
​hhhhhhh ​
​hhhhhh  ​
​hhhhh   ​
​hhhh    ​
per-
perspec-
​perspec-
​perspective
​keeps
​on
​slip-
​ slipping
​through
​my
​           H​
​          HA​
​         HAA​
​        HAAA​
​       HAAAA​
​      HAAAAA​
​     HAAAAAA​
​    HAAAAAAA​
​   HAAAAAAAA​
​  HAAAAAAAAA​
​ HAAAAAAAAAa​
​HAAAAAAAAAaa​
​AAAAAAAAAaaa​
​AAAAAAAAaaaa​
​AAAAAAAaaaaa​
​AAAAAAaaaaaa​
​AAAAAaaaaaaa​
​AAAAaaaaaaaa​
​AAAaaaaaaaaa​
​AAaaaaaaaaaa​
​Aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaaaaaa​
​aaaaaaaaaaan​
​aaaaaaaaaand​
​aaaaaaaaandd​
​aaaaaaaandds​
​aaaaaaandds ​
​aaaaaandds  ​
​aaaaandds   ​
​aaaandds    ​
------------------------------------------------
​aaandds     ​
​aandds      ​
​andds      ​​
Fear it, what you want is near it
But you're really trying
To get away from it
(away from it)
Basic instincts overpowering
You still have this owing
(owing)
When this could be good enough for us
I ain't gonna be taken down
So choose something to believe in
You know we give life it's meaning, oh
If I search my feelings, I don't know
And it's beyond comprehension
You know I don't sense the tension, oh
In place of redemption, I let go
And well, I spent so much time with the don't care crown
That I don't care how it's been weighing me down
And I can't be open in my heart now
I'm feeling nothing at all
I ain't lettin' my spirits down
'Cause ain't much matter that much I found
I'm the dude with the don't care crown
And I ain't gonna be taken down
I ain't gonna be taken down
And I ain't gonna be taken DOWN
Don't go getting mistaken now
DOWN
I ain't gonna be taken down
'Cause ain't much matter that much I found
------------------------------------------------
Yeah, if this is the last time, last time
Last time, last time, last time, last time, last time, la- la- la- la-
Last time, last time, last time, last time, last time, last time,
last time, la- la- la- la-
Was there something in my walk
How I talk, giving off the wrong energy?
Was there something in my stride
Too much pride, telling you to back down?
Slowly, slowly, you became my enemy
But you can't, you can't, seem to get enough of me
So if this is the last time
I guess I better make it worthwhile
Yеah, if this is the last time
I guess I bеtter give it my all
So if this is the last time
I guess I better make it worthwhile
Yеah, if this is the last time
I guess I bеtter give it my all
Yeah, if this is the last time, last time, last-
I guess I better make it worthwhile
Yеah, if this is the last time
I guess I bеtter give it my all
If this is the last time, last time, last-
I guess I better make it worthwhile
Yеah, if this is the last time
But, God, I wish I had you
I guess I bеtter give it my all
Yeah, if this is the last time, last time
But, God, I wish I had you
Last time, last time, last time, last time, last time, la- la- la- la-
I wish I had you
Last time, last time, last time, last time, last time, last time
Last time, LAST TIME
I wish I had you
Last time, last time, last time, last time, last time, last time
last time, la- la- la- la-
I wish I had you
But, God, I wish I had you
Last time, last time, last time, last time, last time, last time
I wish I had-
I wish I had you
But, God, I wish I had you
Keep up with-, Keep up-, Keep up-, -with the flow, -with the flow
The flow, the flow, the flow, keep up with the flow
Keep up with-, Keep up-, Keep up-, Keep up-, Keep up-, Keep up-
Can't keep up with the flow
Keep up with the flow, ow, ow, ow, ow
Keep up with the flow
Keep up with the flow, ow, ow
Sick of all your trash
[Romanized subtitles were made by @Klike on YouTube]
jinjja neujeottanikka
진짜 늦었다니까
neol mitji ana You know why
널 믿지 않아 You know why
nal sogeottaneun geol ara
날 속였다는 걸 알아
bigeugeun wae sarange mokshinde?
비극은 왜 사랑의 몫인데?
seulpeun epik sok geu kkeuteul bogo inne
슬픈 에픽 속 그 끝을 보고 있네
hanttaeneun naui Shawty salajyeo jullae jeoli
한때는 나의 Shawty 사라져 줄래 저리
Don’t think about calling
neon mot beotigetji jipchakppunigetji
넌 못 버티겠지 집착뿐이겠지
nacheoreom jalhan saram eopseul geonikka
나처럼 잘한 사람 없을 거니까
neodo cham pigonhaetji jeonbu kkumyeodaeni
너도 참 피곤했지 전부 꾸며대니
meoritsok kkwaena eojireowosseulgeoya
머릿속 꽤나 어지러웠을거야
-call me
Don’t call me
(micheosseo neon)
(미쳤어 넌)
Don’t call me
(You don’t know, you waste my time)
(neukkyeobwa neon chweagiya)
(느껴봐 넌 최악이야)
Don’t call me
Don’t call-
(Wait, I hate your call)
끝났어 너의 Love
kkeunnasseo neoye Love
Don’t want it now ooh
사랑하면 보내줘
saranghamyeon bonaejweo
Don’t want it now ooh
끝났어 너의 Love
kkeunnasseo neoye Love
Don’t want it now ooh
사랑하면 보내줘
saranghamyeon bonaejweo
Don’t want it now ooh
끝났어 너의
kkeunnasseo neoye
Love
Don’t want it now ooh
사랑하면 보내줘
saranghamyeon bonaejweo
Don’t want it now ooh
끝났어 너의 Love
kkeunnasseo neoye Love
Don’t want it now ooh
사랑하면 보내줘
saranghamyeon bonaejweo
*YEEEAAA*
All the time you've swept away
Has come to catch up to you
I patiently have waited to see
The dark rain over me
In the night
Never gonna give you up
Haha get rick rolled bozo
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around and desert you
Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
In the night
Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around and desert you
In the night
Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye
Never gonna tell a lie and hurt you
In the night
👍
LETS GO