Closed Captions - MitchSirco
I've been tryna get my weary head right
Looking out across that shoreline
Lonely little orange boat light
Heading out for somewhere new
If I lean into my so-called breakdown
I could build myself back up now
Better than before, you’ll see now
I should set sail soon too
And I
try
But nothing's getting through
Un
Uncer
Uncertain
Uncertain life
I’m telling you
How I’m gonna keep
Soon as I let
I feel the bad times
How I’m gonna keep
Soon as I let
I feel the bad times
Coming on
Could I find out what it’s meant to feel like?
Make a choice and just be right
Paddle my way through these times
Tossed about by the wake
'Cause I only want to raise my anchor
And hold myself to a standard
Probably wouldn't need a map, just
A point that I need to make
And I
try
But the winds don't blow my way
I need
some
something
something that’s
something that’s mine
Behind my sails
How I’m gonna keep
Soon as I let
I feel the bad times
How I’m gonna keep
No, I can’t let
I feel the bad times
Yeah,
Yeah, yeah
Oh yeah,
Oh yeah, ooh
Yeah,
Yeah, yeah
Oh yeah,
Oh yeah, ooh
Maybe the headwind’s from acceleration
And all I need’s determination
To hold my bearing and keep it bold
There’s still so many problems I should solve
So I’ll be rushing toward some horizon
Or something I can keep my eyes on
There’s some way I could reach my prize even though
know
How I’m gonna keep
movin' on
Soon as I let
go
I feel the bad times
coming on
know
How I’m gonna keep
movin' on
Soon as I let
go
Feel the bad times
coming on
Yeah,
Yeah, Oh
Yeah, yeah
Oh yeah,
Oh yeah, ooh
Closed Captions - MitchSirco