Subtitles - MitchSirco
Subtitles - MitchSirco - Enjoy :)
What if I told you, I'm to blame?
What if I hold you down 'til the end of days?
I need you, you, you right here
I need-
I'm not giving up no, I will not go
Walking tightropes over the lion's cage
Ooooh-ooh, running in circles trying to fan the flames
I'm out of my mind, living in the memory, yeah
Ooh-ooh-ooh the hours just fall like the rain in the dark
I need you, you, you right here
I need-
If you could just see
how much you need me
I would sleep easier
Oh
A bed full of secrets,
dark lullabies
I want your body near
Oh
The sky fell down and I kinda thought, no big deal
She said she'd rather meet the devil
than be dealin' with these credit card bills
And well, home ain’t home
till it’s somewhere that you’d take a fresh kill
She says, don't push me 'cause I'll freak out
and you know that I will, she will
Yeah, nothin's workin', oh, the pain
We numb the hurting, sweet novocaine
I'm always searchin' and I never change
We might need somethin' else
(But I don't know what)
(But I don't know-)
WOOO
(But I don't know what)
(But I don't- )
See, when the sky fell down
I was kinda like, yeah, that works
(yeah, that works)
I guess I see you 'round
sometime when it doesn't just hurt
(when it doesn't just hurt)
And when it's all gone wrong
and you know it won't get no worse
(yeah, that works)
So yeah, I bide my time
as I try and weaponize my curse
it's thankless work
Yeah, nothin's workin', oh, the pain
We numb the hurting, sweet novocaine
I'm always searchin' and I never change
We might need somethin' else
(But I don't know what)
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
We're falling through the light
Well, isn't life just weird though?
Are you having fun, yeah?
Where did the last year go?
Surely it went somewhere
And all my time is wasted,
And we're all goin' nowhere
Not sure I can take this,
But I don't wanna go there
We slip away, yeah
Let gravity defy
We're falling through the light
We slip away, yeah
Let gravity defy
We're falling through the light
We're falling through the Light
We're falling through the LIght
We're falling through the LIGht
We're falling through the LIGHt
We're falling through the LIGHT
We're falling through the LIGHTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTTTT
Cuz I'm always
in my mind
Out of sight
Let me out, I'll survive
This constant noise is so damn loud
I need something to fade it out
One hunnid
This mic is too high
Drop it, drop it, drop it
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I just been livin' la vida bankroll,
how the sayin' go
Got it flooded to my ankles,
need a raincoat
Pair of boots and a dang boat,
gotta stay float
I might pull up in a stagecoach
playin' Beethov'
(whoa)
Didn't think that it would work
(yeah)
Now they comin' out the woodwork
(whoa)
Built up my own platform,
could say I'm into Woodward
Made this song go viral,
probably off of some footwork
Well, either that or the hook worked
(wait)
Always think of the hook first
(go)
Now I gotta make a bag
just to keep the lights on
I'm on your desktop,
I'm a icon
They say, "Hi, Con', could you put a price on?"
I said, "I ain't sellin' nothin', these are my songs"
Been in my bag, got a satchel pack,
gimme a chance
(acid rap)
Carry the weight, no fragile bag,
fact the cap
(that's a fact)
Even my cap'll snap a fact,
me and my gang like Rascal Flatts
Graduated like tassel hats,
back-to-back
I just been liv-
Come play my game
Inhale, inhale
I just been liv-
You′re the victim
Come play my game
I just been liv-
Exhale, exhale, exhale
I just been livin' la vida bankroll,
how the sayin' go
Got it flooded to my ankles,
need a raincoat
Pair of boots and a dang boat,
gotta stay float
I might pull up in a stagecoach
playin' Beethov'
I just been livin' la vida bankroll,
how the sayin' go
Got it flooded to my ankles,
need a raincoat
Pair of boots and a dang boat,
gotta stay float
I might pull up in a stagecoach
playin' Beethov'
(whoa)
How you goin' off like that?
Off-white kicks and an off-white hat
Ain't start like that but them things just dirty
Lot to unpack like I just got back
I could say "Hi" but it's just too flirty
Fly by-by, got a bird in the cinema
Live it up, clouds, dust when I kick it up
Fill it up, tank ain't big enough
(what? What?)
Eyes on me, so I gotta
Make a bag
Come play my game
just to keep the lights on
I'm on your desktop,
Inhale, inhale
I'm a icon
You′re the victim
They say, "Hi, Con', could you put a price on?"
Come play my game
I said, "I ain't sellin' nothin', these are my songs"
Exhale, exhale, exhale
Come play my game
Breathe with me
Breathe the pressure
Come play my game, I′ll test ya
Psychosomatic, addict, insane
Breathe the pressure
Come play my game, I′ll test ya
Psycho- Psychosomatic, addict, insane
Come play my game
Inhale, inhale
You′re the victim
Come play my game
Exhale, exhale, exhale
Yo
You know what time it is
(Okay)
It's Virus Syndicate, Eliminate
Disciple
(*vomiting*)
Going in for the kill
Aim for the throat like a drunk at the wheel
Hungry, I'm going in for a meal
Aim for a penny, nah, I aim for a mil'
(Nah, I aim for a mil)
Yeah, I'm in for the whole nine yards
(Yards)
And I've already told you before,
nobody got flow like ours
Nobody got flow like ours
Pack in my pocket, I pick up the bill
Packin' the product, they popping my pill
Hot on the topic, unstoppable skill
Now put the fuckers at the top of the bill
(Top of the bill)
I never get any chill, man, I'm unstoppable still
They know the drill, dripping with lyrical skill
Fuck it, I love it, I'm ill
I eliminate them,
sixteen bars to obliterate them
All the MCs try and imitate them,
I told 'em before, I eliminate them
I eliminate them, I eliminate them
I eliminate them
I told 'em before, I eliminate
I told 'em before, I e—
(Drop, drop, drop, drop)
Told-told 'em before, I eliminate them
I told 'em before, I e—
I eliminate- (Drop)
I eliminate- (Drop, drop)
Told-told 'em before, I eliminate them
Uh, yah
Yeah, yuh
Yeah, Riddle or, rhythm or, neither nor
Shit's all sick, rigor mortis
In it for big applause
Any more chicken or beef for the walrus, uh
Keep the oder rigged
and awfully menacing
When I torture
beats, leave no more seats
See, my steezy bought me these,
keep walkin'
Yeah, phlegm in your wellingtons again
Medicine's irrelevant by then
Penicillin, pessimism, and
I feed on that
Mean streak machine rap
Cock back, click clack,
I bleed black
Roll in slow motion with my sh-
Yeah, Cock back, click clack,
I bleed black
Hasta la vista, baby
Yeah, Cock back, click clack,
I bleed black
Uh, uh, jealousy gettin' you nowhere,
best look away
It's me or me or me or me
Shit, I reckon you should swing or step aside, bro
Don't recognize those
I'm especially so special
It's essentially the best to be
me entering in these kicks
Like, which ability will he pick?
Cock back, click clack,
I bleed black
What you know about rollin' down in the deep?
When your brain goes numb,
you can call that mental freeze
When these people talk too much,
put that shit in slow motion, yeah
I feel like an astronaut in the ocean, ayy
What you know about rollin' down in the deep?
When your brain goes numb,
you can call that mental freeze
When these people talk too much,
put that shit in slow motion, yeah
I feel like an astronaut in the ocean
She say that I'm cool
(damn straight)
I'm like, "Yeah, that's true"
(that's true)
I believe in G-O-D
(ayy)
Don't believe in T-H-O-T
She keep playing me dumb
(play me)
I'ma play her for fun
(uh-huh)
Y'all don't really know my mental
Lemme give you the picture like stencil
Falling out, in a drought
No flow, rain wasn't pouring down
(pouring down)
See, that pain was all around
See, my mode was kinda lounged
Didn't know which-which way to turn
Flow was cool but I still felt burnt
Energy up, you gon' feel my surge
I'ma kill everything like this purge
(ayy)
Let's just get this straight for a second,
I'ma work
Even if I don't get paid for progression,
I'ma get it
Everything that I do is electric
I'ma keep it in a motion
(yeah)
Keep it moving like kinetic, ayy
(yeah, yeah, yeah)
Put this shit in a frame,
better know I don't blame
Everything that I say,
man, I seen you deflate
Let me elevate,
this ain't a prank
Have you walkin' on a plank
la-la-la-la-la, like
Both hands together,
God, let me pray
(now let me pray)
Uh, I've been going right, right around, call that relay
Uh, I've been going right, ri  ght around, call that relay
Just come outside
For the night
(Yeah)
Take your time
Get your light
(Yeah)
Johnny Dang, yeah, yeah
I been out geekin'
Blast off
Passin' everybody I'm passin' you every body
With a homi gonna have to blame it on me
when I'm masked off
And it must stang bein' gassed up
Runnin' laps steady, tryna ad verb
Motherfucking Nascar
Leavin' you spinnin' around,
still in the ground
Feelin' my rounds
Make it really a pound
I put my hand
and it's liftin' you up to the ceiling
And you a fan there spillin' your guts
Rising up from the fire
I'm a free bird
Twenty-thousand miles an hour
I fly though the ether
I'm high up in the sky
Look how little thee Earth
It's a comet, it's a rocket
It's my middle finger
I'm Falcon Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Yeah, Falcon Heavy
I'm Falcon Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Yeah, Falcon Heavy, Heavy
And I'm headed to the stars to give me space X
I'm a predator with these bars
Yes, I'm an apex
I'm Falcon Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Falcon Heavy
Yeah
Imagine me giving a fuck
Sittin' around here,
talkin' 'bout my feelings and such
Really I'm touched
You really a cuck
I bet a Heckler & Koch
will have you feelin' like a million bucks
Feelin' you up
It ain't unleaded, I done dead'ed
Anyone who come revin' you don' get it
I'm tellin' you to run like
"dumb, diddy-dumb, diddy-diddy-dumb"
Fuck, Even Rev Run said it
I'm ridiculous in my rage
When I'm feelin' nickel less in my cage
Wanna raise an AR in your zone
But I stick lyrics to the page
That will have you feelin' pistol whipped
I'm gifted with
the sickend wit
the shit I spit
Gonna save me the splitting, wrist
Critics diss and miss the hits
Still I hit 'em in the face
It's violence and silence
anytime that lyin's involved
To the self,
no one finds it but inside it
hiding in the island you are
But I can't define who you are
When you make it part of the process
You can put it in the arts for the awe
Or put in the bars for the awe shit
RISING UP FROM THE FIRE
I'm a free bird
TWENTY-THOUSAND MILES AN HOUR
I fly through the ether
I'M HIGH UP IN THE SKY
Look how little thee Earth
IT'S A COMET, IT'S A ROCKET
It's my middle finger
I'm Falcon Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Yeah, Falcon Heavy
I'm Falcon Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Yeah, Falcon Heavy
And I'm headed to the stars to give me space like an X
I'm a predator with these bars
Yes, I'm an a-a-apex
I'm Falcon Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Falcon Heavy
Now- Heavy
(Falcon Heavy)
Falcon Heavy
Now run it back, I'm an apex
That's an x ape with a cape for
The escape, yes, I'ma take X
And then add space for Miss Baker
That's an ad-space for this finger
Gonna have to face up that I'm flyer
While the flat earthers will have you certain
And back to searchin' for fire
Fuck you
One-two
I'm up over your head like them bunny ears
All the rappers you compare me to
I'm like ahead by 10 or 20 years
That's 20 on the gears and me
I got like, uh,
25 on the mic
You put 20 and I in your ears
And that's like 25 to life
You'll get dropped when the-
Everybody party
You'll get dropped when the beat gets rough
Back to the-
Leroooooy
One, two, three, go!
You'll get dropped when the-
You'll get dropped when the beat gets rough
Back to the-
🫵
You know you got me so distracted
I'm waving your hair all around
It's you in every reflection
Oh no, I can't keep my eyes on the ground
You con-trol my mind
You control my mind -
And you keep me up that night
And my heart beats to working overtime
But this is Paradise
You con-trol my mind
You control my mind -
And you keep me up that night
And it feels like a glitch inside my mind
(Paradise)
This is Paradise
There's no doubt
I can tell
you're acting your heart out
And she's addicted
Obsessed like,
"I know I can fix him"
She's got hearts in her eyes
And she draws me
kissing other guys
Her love,
the type
Where she don't know
where to draw the line
(Oh)
Cheerleader
Thought she needed me,
but I need her
It's not
fa- fa- fa- fa- fa- fa- fa- fa- fa-
'Cause I knew you like the back of my-
Well, don't you
ca- ca- ca- ca- ca-?
I gave you everything, ah
Now I feel you even when you're not there
It's beating me down
And it's freaking me out, yeah
(Everything makes no sense)
(And I just can't see the difference)
(And I been hoping that tomorrow might save me, yeah)
You could say that I'm out past misery
And I'm outclassed viciously by the hard times
Could be me or my bad mind
I wish to be with my people
Trying stuff for no reason
Might discover some meaning
Why am I here overthinking?
I'm just tryna figure it out
I been searching and can't find a reason
Why I'm the mess I am now
How am I supposed to relax through competing
With all of the stress and the doubt
I'm too close to the canvas
I gotta step back
I can do this but how
I guess I'll keep trying to
FIGURE IT OUT
Oh, there's gotta be some kinda reason
Why I've been
FEELING SO DOWN
I did everything right
but it still feels like the
SKY'S FALLING DOWN
It's my enemy brain, ain't cooperating
It's
BEATING ME DOWN
oh and it's
FREAKING ME OUT
We're getting closer
Yeah, yeah
(Enemy brain, enemy brain)
(It’s always the same, always the same)
We're getting closer
(Enemy brain, enemy brain)
(It’s always the same, always the same)
Closer
(Enemy brain, enemy brain)
We're getting CLOSER
Long Legged Larry was a frog at the pond
Jump so high,
might miss him while he's gone
Jump over anything,
even King Kong
Jumping Jack Flash was his favorite song
We're getting closer
Now once upon a time
there was a cat in a tree
Chased a squirrel up,
been stuck since three
The fireman came, said
"It's too high for me"
How's that cat gonna ever get free?
Young Jack Turner was a staple on the block
Said he knew about a frog with them XL hop
The neighbors startеd laughing,
but Jackie wouldn't stop
Ran off, came back,
guess who hе got?
Well, it was Long Legged Larry,
didn't open his mouth
Like a rocket to the moon
through a cumulus cloud
Touch down safe,
lay the scaredy-cat on the ground
If you listen real close,
you can still hear the crowd
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go Larry
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go, go, go
Larry doesn't care
Jump so high
grow a beard in the air
Jump over anything,
even Times Square
Yelling "Long Legged Larry for mayor!, Here! Here!"
Now once upon a time
there was a princess in a cell
In the tower of a castle,
through a forest on a hill
Half the men that ever sought her out
had fallen ill
All the men that ever
tried to climb the wall had fell
Handful gather
at the base of the place
Each claim way braver
than the bravest you've faced
Bunch of dingbats yapping
about saving the day
But wait, a silhouetted amphibian face in the haze
Well, it was Long Legged Larry
on the back of a steed
Leapt up yelling "Jordan!"
Kiss the girl on the cheek
"Jordan!"
Touch down safe,
show the lady back to her peeps
If you listen real close,
you can still hear the streets
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go Larry
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go, go, go
Larry, go Larry, go, go, go Larry
Yeah
Larry's on the case
Jump so high
pluck a star out of space
Jump over anything,
even Salt Lake
Jump into the mosh pit,
jump out of a cake
Now once upon a time
there was a circus in town
Some went for the cotton candy,
some for the clowns
But the high wire act
was the most profound
Had a poodle on a unicycle,
rose in her mouth
Yeah
trendsetter, woah
League of my own,
it don't get better, no
Read what I wrote,
I'm a bestseller, yeah
Reach for my goals,
hit it dead center
Hit it dead center
Bullseye, hit it the most,
therе's no misses
Something like fish in a barrеl,
it's no different
Blindfold on me,
I still got the most vision
Trendsetter, told 'em before
but they don't listen
Batter better, bring a better bat
because I'm bigger, better
Solo singles, selling several shows
out every single second
Peter Piper picked a
peck of pickled peppers
Connor came and crushed the competition
Hope they get the message
Look
Living it fast,
been in my Eminem bag
I never go slow
Thinking I'll crash,
end up a thing in the past
They know I won't though
Big fish catching me,
they gon' need a bigger boat
Ironic how the world stops
when I spin a globe
(Spin a globe)
Always showing up
(Right)
Last year's songs still holding up
(Uh-uh)
See the name now
and they know what's up
(Right)
Price hit the top
(Yeah, ay, woah, uh)
and it's going up
I'm a
trendsetter, woah
(trendsetter)
League of my own,
it don't get better, no
(It don't get better)
Read what I wrote,
I'm a bestseller, yeah
(I'm a bestseller)
Reach for my goals,
hit it dead center
(What?)
Hit it dead center
Yeah, ay,
trendsetter, woah
League of my own,
it don't get better, no
(Nah)
Read what I wrote,
I'm a bestseller, yeah
Reach for my goals,
hit it dead center
Hit it dead center
(Yeah)
Ne, oh,
trendsetter, woah
(trendsetter)
League of my own,
it don't get better, no
(It don't get better)
Read what I wrote,
I'm a bestseller, yeah
(I'm a bestseller)
Reach for my goals,
hit it dead center
(What?)
Hit it dead center
Yeah, ay,
trendsetter, woah
League of my own,
it don't get better, no
(Nah)
Read what I wrote,
I'm a bestseller, yeah
Reach for my goals,
hit it dead center
Hit it dead center
(Yeah)
Hee ohh
Yall, im releasing AKs, my AKAs
Will prob a quick button,
and then to your birthdays
-days, -days, -days, -days
I got a slumber that’ll put you to sleep
I shock
This is hard shock
We make them bring a drink
(This is hard shock)
(We make them bring a drink)
I got a slumber that'll put you to sleep
Listen
FUCKING GOLD DUST