Thought I'd figure this all out on my own
Started hoping we just let it grow
Now the water's slowly getting cold
As we lose each day a little more
Caught up again, we're rusting down another high
Just burning up like satellites across the sky
I know I keep pretending that we're doing fine
Lost
Lost in
Lost in us
All I wanted
Holding up for days just to get by
Reaching out just for something to feel alive
All I wanted was you
And I let it slip away
-was you
And I can't make you stay
Caught up again, just chase around another life
So holding on like shadows fading in the night
I know I keep pretending but we're not alright
Not
Not en
Not enough
All I wanted
Holding up for days just to get by
Reaching out just for something to feel alive
All I wanted was you
And I let it slip away
-was you
And I can't make you stay
All I wanted was you
And I let it slip away
-was you
And I can't make you stay