Subtitles - MitchSirco
Drank from the
Posion oak
Cambridge left
Before we spoke
I don't wanna be displaced
The heart that can't be replaced
So, What if I just erased?
Go ahead, I'm already a waste
:3
LET'S GO
I'm already a
I don't wanna be displaced
The heart that can't be replaced
So, what if I just erased?
Go ahead, I'm already a waste
I'm already a
I'm already a waste
We slip away, yeah
Let gravity defy
We're falling through the light
We slip away, yeah
Let gravity defy
We're falling through the light
I CAN'T WAKE UP
Gravity defy
IN THE MORNING
I CAN'T WAKE UP
IT'S FUCKING BORI-
We're falling through the light
IT'S FUCKING BO-
I'm already a
Yeah, I'm already a waste
We slip away, yeah
Let gravity defy
We're falling through the light
We slip away, yeah
Let gravity defy
We're falling through the light
We're falling through the Light
We're falling through the LIght
We're falling through the LIGht
We're falling through the LIGHt
We're falling through the LIGHT
We're falling through the LIGHTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTTTTT
We're falling through the LIGHTTTTTTTT
I don't wanna be displaced
The heart that can't be replaced
So, what if I just erased?
Go ahead, I'm already a waste
I'm already a
I'm already a waste
Feel the thunder shake the open ground
Won’t give in I’m fighting for the crown
Gravity defy
Heavy clouds are way above my head
Like all of my regrets
And things I never said now
Got a feeling shiver in my bones
Something’s coming but nobody knows
Angels rage they come down from the sky
To fix these broken wings
And show me how to fly
I- I- I- I-
I burn the sky
I see the fire in your
Eye- Eye- Eye- Eyes
I come alive
And I feel like I could spread my wings and fly
So if you’re ever feeling down, I’m right here
Our story has only just become,
a new horizon
A new horizon
Looks like I hit a controller bug
I have to unplug my controller
and plug it back in
I think my FLX6 has a bug in it
Take it slow,
So I gotta do that every now and then
To keep on following the yellow lines that guide us down the road
Alright, were good
The city lights,
Were gonna do some doubles that I've never done before
are slowly shifting into darkness as we drive into the night
Cuz why the fuck not
Let's gooo! Let's see those doubles!
So if you’re ever feeling down, I’m right here
Our story has only just become,
A new horizon
You stopped lovin' mе on the dark nights (Dark nights)
a new horizon
Now you won't kiss me in the sunlight
Last summеr, I knew you'd leave me (Leave me)
a new horizon
'Cause lovin' me isn't easy
If you wanted to talk, you would have texted
If I wanted to stop, I woulda let it go
But I get it, it's alright
'Cause I can't keep my shit together
Say "Fuck it," yeah, can't debate that
Don't want shit to get better
'Cause it'd make me forget it all and I hate that
Last summer, everything was easy
(Easy)
We had it all, didn't we, baby?
No wonder, you couldn't keep me
(Keep me)
It got harder than you thought it would be
You stopped lovin' mе on the dark nights
(Dark nights)
Now you won't kiss me in the sunlight
Last summеr, I knew you'd leave me
(Leave me)
'Cause lovin' me isn't easy
Last summer, everything was easy
(Easy)
We had it all, didn't we, baby?
No wonder, you couldn't keep me
(Keep me)
It got harder than you thought it would be
You stopped lovin' mе on the dark nights
(Dark nights)
Now you won't kiss me in the sunlight
Last summеr, I knew you'd leave me
(Leave me)
'Cause lovin' me isn't easy
Yea, The sky fell down and I kinda thought, no big deal
She said she'd rather meet the devil
than be dealin' with these credit card bills
And well, home ain’t home
till it’s somewhere that you’d take a fresh kill
She says, don't push me 'cause I'll freak out
and you know that I will, she will
Yeah, nothin's workin', oh, the pain
We numb the hurting, sweet novocaine
I'm always searchin' and I never change
We might need somethin' else
But i don't know what
But i don't know- WOOO
But i don't-
See, when the sky fell down
I was kinda like, yeah, that works
Yeah, that works
I guess I see you 'round sometime
when it doesn't just hurt
When it doesn't just hurt
And when it's all gone wrong
and you know it won't get no worse
Yeah, that works
So yeah, I bide my time
as I try and weaponize my curse
It's thankless work
Yeah, nothin's workin', oh, the pain
We numb the hurting, sweet novocaine
I'm always searchin' and I never change
We might need somethin' else
not let it slide
Glad I came for the hype
Just the vibe
Not a clue where I'm born and I just came for the ride
(But I don't know what)
Man are outside, man are inside
I swear I locked away the beast but man was coming alive
(Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah)
Look in my eyes, see the look in my eyes
See the fire it's no surprise that I'm up on a rise
Yeah I fight to the finish I will not take a dive
You can take all of your shots but they will not take my pride
Well, isn't life just weird though?
Are you having fun, yeah?
Where did the last year go?
Surely it went somewhere
And all my time is wasted,
And we're all goin' nowhere
Not sure I can take this,
But I don't wanna go there
I will not let it slide
Better run better hide
Making money I'm connected like the bees of the hive
You don't wanna see me with couple G's in your drive
Yeah we're keeping it nice
That's the key to survive
I should keep with the vibe
Better pick up the pace
I get down on my face
Now I'm leading the race
Got em' chased to the ace
Got a lot on my head
I could do with the space
-do with the space
Long Legged Larry was a frog at the pond
Jump so high, might miss him while he gone
Jump over anything, even King Kong
Jumping Jack Flash was his favorite song
Now once upon a time there was a cat in a tree
Chased a squirrel up, been stuck since three
The fireman came, said "It's too high for me"
*Thats to high*
How's that cat gonna ever get free?
Young Jack Turner was a staple on the block
Said he knew about a frog with an XL hop
The neighbors startеd laughing, but Jackie wouldn't stop
Ran off, came back, guess who hе got?
Well, it was Long Legged Larry, didn't open his mouth
Like a rocket to the moon through a cumulus cloud
Touch down safe, lay the scaredy-cat on the ground
If you listen real close, you can still hear the crowd
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go Larry
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go, go, go
Larry doesn't care
Jump so high grow a beard in the air
Jump over anything, even Times Square
Yelling "Long Legged Larry for mayor!, Here! Here!"
Now once upon a time there was a princess in a cell
In the tower of a castle, through a forest on a hill
Half the men that ever sought her out had fallen ill
All the men that ever tried to climb the wall had fell
Handful gather at the base of the place
Each claim way braver than the bravest you've faced
Bunch of dingbats yapping about saving the day
But wait, a silhouetted amphibian face in the haze
Well, it was Long Legged Larry on the back of a steed
Leapt up yelling "Jordan!" Kiss the girl on the cheek
Jordan!
Touch down safe, show the lady back to her peeps
If you listen real close, you can still hear the streets
ARE YOU READYYY
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go Larry
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go, go, go
Larry, go Larry, go, go, go Larry
This is the crab rave
Go Larry, go Larry, go, go, go, go, go
Yeah
Larry's on the case
Jump so high pluck a star out of space
Jump over anything, even Salt Lake
Jump into the mosh pit, jump out of a cake
Now once upon a time there was a circus in town
Some went for the cotton candy, some for the clowns
But the high wire act was the most profound
Had a poodle on a unicycle, rose in her mouth
Ten o'clock show get the poodle in position
Ten seconds in the unicycle starts tipping
Now the poodle barely clinging to the wire by her mittens
But what the heck is that thing in the distance?
Ribbit, Long Legged Larry, a sight for sore eyes
Known to give a dog a ride seconds after he arrives
Touch down safe, give her some kibbles and rawhide
If you listen real close, you can still hear the vibe
Go-
ARE YOU READYYY
This is the crab rave
Sweet nothings in one ear and out the other
So long I lived in fear of getting closer to you
And relying on your praise
Though it's diluting with the days
That passes by
To remind myself I still know how to fly
Oooooh
It's hard to breathe
And I can't believe I'm worth anything at all
And if these fragile wings can carry me along up to the sun
Can I bear the weight of the fall back down to you?
I wake up so convinced the tap’s stopped flowing
Got this incessant need to keep on showing
I'm fine, so I drain the river dry
Impressing a hundred thousand eyes
A sacrifice to remind myself I still know how to fly
And if these fragile wings can carry me along up to the sun
Can I bear the weight of the fall back down to you?
As much as it pains you
You ask me to stay
Both stuck in a moment
We both look away
I'll break any day now
And now you don't wanna say
You pulled me in closer
And I'm fine either way
I bet if it worked
It’d be worse and I’d try to fly away
I bet, if it hurts
Then you learn and you try to find a way
I hold down when it's hopeless
Hold down when it's hopeless
Guess I'll never change
Never ask if that's where you wanna be
Pulling back
Get away from me
I hold down when it's hopeless
Hold down when it's hopeless
Guess I'll never change
I threw my phone into the sea
Simple human being
Wouldn't know how to brush my teeth
Without asking my team
Living in the afterglow
Of everything you feel
But, baby, I'm a short-lived joke
As soulless as I seem
And I'm everything you talk about
Why should you keep letting yourself be let down?
If I'm everything you talk about
I'm in the mirror, baby, let it all out
Knock yourself out
-yourself out
Listen
Don't know my schedule on the fifth
Bitch, I'm Taylor Swift
Got a hundred million on my wrist
Physically sick
Crying at the airport
"I'm sorry, can I get a pic?"
Telling me a sad story
Another reason not to quit
And I'm everything you talk about
Why should you keep letting yourself be let down?
If I'm everything you talk about
I'm in the mirror, baby, let it all out
I wear a big smile, got a drink in my hand
I got a face tattoo, I'm not a regular man
You gotta hold on, I'll tell you 'bout it again
I got a brand new feeling in the back of my head
I wear a big smile, got a drink in my hand
I drive a new Bugatti, not a Mercedes Benz
You gotta hold on, I'll tell you 'bout it again
I got a brand new feeling in the back of my head
And I'm everything you talk about
Why should you keep letting yourself be let down?
If I'm everything you talk about
I'm in the mirror, baby, let it all out
Knock yourself out
Oa-oa aa
Dansa med oss
Klappa era händer
Gör som vi gör
Ta några steg åt vänster
Lyssna och lär
Missa inte chansen
Nu är vi här me
Caramelldansen
Oa-oa aa
O-o-oa-oa
O-o-oa-oa aa
Det blir en sensation överallt förstås
På fester kommer alla att släppa loss
Kom igen
Nu tar vi stegen om igen (Oh-wa-ohwa-ah)
Let's Go
Så rör på era fötter (Oa-a-a)
Och vicka era höfter (O-la-la-la)
Gör som vi
Till denna melodi
Så kom och
Dansa med oss
Klappa era händer
Gör som vi gör
Ta några steg åt vänster
Lyssna och lär
Missa inte chansen
Nu är vi här me
Caramelldansen
Last Friday night
Yeah, we danced on tabletops,
and we took too many shots
Think we kissed, but I forgot last Friday night
Lyssna och lär
Yeah, we maxed our credit cards
Missa inte chansen
and got kicked out of the bar
Nu är vi här me
So we hit the boulevard last Friday night
Caramelldansen
Oa-oa aa
O-o-oa-oa
If it hadn't been for Cotton-Eye Joe
I'd been married long time ago
Where did you come from, where did you go?
O-o-oa-oa aa
Where did you come from, Cotton-Eye Joe?
If it hadn't been for Cotton-Eye Joe
Lyssna och lär
Missa inte chansen
I'd been married long time ago
Where did you come from, where did you go?
Nu är vi här me
Caramelldansen
Where did you come-
Dansa med oss
Klappa era händer
Gör som vi gör
Ta några steg åt vänster
Lyssna och lär
Missa inte chansen
Nu är vi här me
Caramelldansen
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Feelin' like a polar bear burnin'
What are we gonna do?
I'm that fake smile gleamin'
Yeah, I'm the lie that you choose to believe in
Guess the truth kinda lost all meanin'
And I'm enjoying the view
Well I've been a lovin' lover
I've been a trusting brother
I'm taking my time to recover
And pickin' it up when I'm better
Oh, there's so much to see in a lifetime
So why does it feel like it flies by?
She's staring me down with the bright eyes
Don't threaten me with a good time
Don't threaten me with a good time)
Stood in the headlights
Holding my hand tight
Don't let go
If you go down,
I'm staying by your side
(-na na na na)
(Na na-na-na na na na na)
If you're going down, I'm going-
Na na-na-na na na na na
If you're going down
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
Na na-na-na na na na na
I'm that hurricane turnin'
If you're going down
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Feelin' like a polar bear burnin'
What are we gonna do?
I'm that fake smile gleamin'
Yeah, I'm the lie that you choose to believe in
Guess the truth kinda lost all meanin'
Call me in the city, call me if you could
And I'm enjoying the view
Everybody in the area
Well I've been a lovin' lover
Call me in the city, call me if you could
I've been a trusting brother
If the brothers gonna help, do not throw
I'm taking my time to recover
Call me in the city, call me if you could
And pickin' it up when I'm better
Everybody in the area
Oh, there's so much to see in a lifetime
Call me in the city, call me if you could
So why does it feel like it flies by?
If the brothers gonna help, do not throw
She's staring me down with the bright eyes
Call me in the city, call me if you could
Don't threaten me with a good time
Everybody in the area
In the city, call me if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
Call me in the city, call me if you-
If the brothers gonna help-
In the city, call me if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
Call me in the city, call me if you-
Everybody in the area-
In the c-, call- if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
Everybody in the area-
Extinction level twenty, fuck a penny for your thoughts
Call me in the city, call me if you could
For the many, not the few, one percent a thing of lore
Everybody in the area-
In the call, if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
The warehouse
In the call, if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
The warehouse
In the call, if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
Like a renegade
In the call, if you-
Brothers gonna help, do not-
Yeah, yeah
Love and care the only option
New world order, vice law the fuckin' problem
See, we can be the change, evolution is solution
Greed, power, money, nothing more than an illusion
Delusion took its toll, banks made the bed
Balance brought the shetty, severed lay the head
Politics ate itself, the people came to live
We're looking to the future like something's gotta give
People power
The warehouse
Like a renegade
People power
Do the math, bitch, do the math
One milly paid in tax, bitch do the math
Did the math, I'm baby Johnny Cash
My girl gon' throw it back
Damn, my life is Cinemax
Holly hell, this smacks
I make hits and you make trash
I'm on vacay do not ask
Poolside eating apple jacks
Shut up bitch
(shut up)
Big deal like Tj Maxx
(Maxx)
Pop some cataracts
Watching Art Attack
(woo)
Nick Cage, how I act
Heavily dislike tax
Got some Asics on my feet, never wear Air Max
I'm in the cut, like a wound
Wake yo' ass up, make some room
In my girl coming soon
I don't fuck with honeymoons
Throw some money on my tomb
Finesse too hard, I'm feeling oom
Girls love me, they wanna spoon
Let me finish, I'll resume
Flame suit, french leather and my girl bad
Gatekeeper say it's open, I ain't calling back
15 minute TED Talk, collecting 40 racks
One milly paid in tax, bitch do the math
Do the math, bitch, do the math
I just curved Cameo
She said I'm her Romeo
(Juliet)
She gon’ split me up and lick me up like Oreo
First global book deal, sell that shit to Indigo
Getting money since I was an itty-bitty embryo
Save my money but I die for the fam
Always make it sail, catamaran
I'll give it it out (krrrr!)
Shawty tryna play some games but I don't play Catan
I'm a plug, she an outlet
Cut out Mr. Middleman
I'll give it it out (krrrr!)
Two step, then I bring it right back
One step, now take it right back
I'll give it it out (krrrr!)
Two step, then I bring it right back
One step, now take it right back
I'll give it it out (krrrr!)
Two step, then I bring it right back
One step, now take it right back
I'll give it it out (krrrr!)
Two step, then I bring it right back
Is full of sin
One step, now take it right back
I'll give it it out (krrrr!)
Imma- Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
The guilty one
Imma- Imma give it- Imma give it- Imma- Imma- Imma give it-
Is full of sin
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
Imma give it to you when you wanted my stuff
Imma give it to you when you wanted- wanted- wanted-
Is full of sin
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
Imma give it to you when you wanted my stuff
Imma- Imma give it- Imma give it- Imma- Imma- Imma give it-
Is full of sin
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
no limit
When I step into the club,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
Imma give it to you when you wanted my stuff
When you see me in the club,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
the party on lock
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
Imma give it to you when you wanted- wanted- wanted-
When I step into the club,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
Imma give it to you when you wanted my stuff
You've got to move with it,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
step with it,
Imma- Imma give it- Imma give it-
no limit
When I step into the club,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
Imma give it to you when you wanted my stuff
When you see me in the club,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
the party on lock
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
Imma give it to you when you wanted- wanted- wanted-
When I step into the club,
Imma give it to you when you wanted there to lie
drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
Imma give it to you when you wanted my stuff
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
no limit
When I step into the-
Wooohoooeuh
WOOH
Born slippy, so look busy
Young scumbag got the keys to the city
I'm knee jerking, black coffee slurping
We're all screwed up but the world's still turnin'
I hug my demons, I fistbump Jesus
I thank Poseidon for a sweet surf season
When I arrive it won't be pretty
From Moscow to the great Mississippi
So
I reckon in 21 seconds
*Crowd singing along*
I’m about to blow this thing straight to the heavens
Still stressin’, Still second guessing
Paid my price but learnt no lesson
So cold, my heavyweight soul
So weighed down by the things that I know
All told I got too bold, Heart of Gold?
No, I do it like that
I do it like that
Like that
(Oh yeah)
(uh)
Space wizards, Hollywood blizzards
Cheatin’ at cards with illuminati lizards
From Indiana out to Valhalla
They know my name
‘cause nobody does it better, yea
And it’s strange but I don’t mind
I drive off the edge of the earth to kill time
The storm’s comin’
You better get runnin’
Wherever I am I’m starting up something
I reckon in 21 seconds
I’m about to blow this thing straight to the heavens
Still stressin’, Still second guessing
Paid my price but learnt no lesson
YEAH
So cold, my heavyweight soul
So weighed down by the things that I know
WOO
All told I got too bold, Heart of Gold?
No, I do it like that
Like that
I do it like that
(Oh yeah)
Like that
I do it like that
(Oh yeah)
(uh)
We set it off and you scramble like you under attack
But dont run that booming sound is just a banging track
Camo krooked Jeru do more damage than a razor back
Space age forget the glock and cock the laser back
Scientifical madness repin stellar weapon carbon black
*realises* Nooo
*chuckles*
So be alarmed we droppin bombs not fiction nothing but fact
I swing the mic and chop it down like a lumberjack
We about to blow it up so where my people at
People at
You know the drill
*chuckles* You know the drill
Oh my god, no fucking way
None other than the illest
Tracker 9 Battery low? (foreshadowing)
Illest
I love it though
of course he can
look at him go
We set it off
WE SET IT OFF
🪑
⬇️ 🪑
You're gonna kick him right off
Oh my god, you have a fucking chair?
🪑
🪑⬅️
None other than the illest
Illest
It's this song!!! YEEES
🪑
🪑⬅️
The fucking chair
Na-Na-Na Na-Na-Na
Solo Killa
Killa
Oh, my water bottle
*laughing*
*more laughing*
None other than the illest
but what do I know
Illest
You take no bullet for me
But I know, and I still care
Illest
Águila del monte
I take you with me wherever I go
I keep you company, but what do I know
Águila del monte
You take no bullet for me
But I know, and I still care
Como el pavo real
Águila del monte
Del monte será
Se le oyen las voces
Como el pavo real
Águila del-
Sientelo
Fuck
Doin-
Doing things in a orderly fashion
Fuck it
Fu- Fu- Fu-
Doing things in a orderly fashion
Fuck it
Doing things in a orderly-
Doing things in a or-
Back with a track called "Driver"
It's the return of the-
I'll have a motherfucking-
Ohhhhhhh
Ohhh shit
*Laughing*
Yo
You know what time it is
Ok
It's Virus Syndicate, Eliminate
Disciple
*Vomiting*
Going in for the kill
Aim for the throat like a drunk at the wheel
Hungry, I'm going in for a meal
Aim for a penny, nah, I aim for a mil'
(nah, I aim for a mil')
Yeah, I'm in for the whole nine yards
(yards)
And I've already told you before,
nobody got flow like ours
Nobody got flow like ours
Pack in my pocket, I pick up the bill
Packin' the product, they popping my pill
Hot on the topic, unstoppable skill
Now put the fuckers at the top of the bill
(Top of the bill)
I never get any chill, man, I'm unstoppable still
They know the drill, dripping with lyrical skill
Fuck it, I love it, I'm ill
I eliminate them, sixteen bars to obliterate them
All the MCs try and imitate them,
I told 'em before, I eliminate them
I eliminate them, I eliminate them
I eliminate them
I told 'em before, I eliminate
I told 'em before, I e-
(Drop, drop, drop, drop)
Told-told 'em before, I eliminate them
I told 'em before, I e-
I eliminate- (Drop)
I eliminate- (Drop, drop)
Told-told 'em before, I eliminate them
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
You better move, move
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
You better move
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
You better move, move
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
You better move, move
Mе e' necesario quе me dejes el control
Cuando jodas, yo ni vuelvo en pie
You better move, move, move, move
(When I push, I feel good)
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
When I push, I feel good
(Y'all ready?)
When I pull, I feel good
( I don't think y'all ready)
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
(Hey Griff, bring in the katz)
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
When I push, I feel good
When I pull, I feel good
When I push, push, push, push, push, push, push
YOOOHOOOHO
Should be good
YOOOOH
When I get high, I get high on speed
Top fuel funny car's a drug for me
My heart, MY HEART
Kickstart my heart
Always got the cops coming after me
Custom built bike doing 103
My heart, MY HEART
Kickstart my heart
Ooh, are you ready girls?
Ooh, are you ready now?
Whoa
yeah
Kickstart my heart, give it a start
Whoa, yeah
Baby, yeah
Skydive naked from an aeroplane
Or a lady with a body from outer space
My heart, MY HEART
Kickstart my heart
Say I got trouble, trouble in my eyes
I'm just looking for another good time
My heart, MY HEART
Kickstart my heart
Yeah, are you ready girls?
Yeah, are you ready now, now, now?
Whoa, yeah
Kickstart my heart, give it a start
Baby
Whoa, yeah
Kickstart my heart, hope it never stops
Baby
YEAH
LET'S GO
Oh god
YEAH
*laughing*
*Tries to close window*
With coffin nails I'll raise the stakes
Making memories you can't erase
I've finally come to see the light
In the night
With coffin nails I'll raise the stakes
Making memories you can't erase
I've finally come to see the light
In the night
Blegh
Hi, are you looking for the other side?
Feel like nothing ever seems quite right?
Are you circling the drainpipe?
Getting off on pain like
You're corrupted?
I need to know where your loyalties lie
Tell me, are you gonna bark or bite?
Do you really wanna twist the knife in the belly
OF the monster?
OF THE monster?
OF THE MONster?
OF THE MONSTER?
Get the fuck up
Wake the fuck up
Wipe the system and
back the fuck up
You're a puppet when thеy cut your strings off
DON'T come crawling back
DON'T COME crawling back
DON'T COME CRAWling back
DON'T COME CRAWLING back
DON'T COME CRAWLING BACK
Kingslayer, destroying castlеs in the sky
Kingslayer, forevermore the apple of my eye
I'd sacrifice my life to find you, angel of the blade
Kingslayer, come and collect us from the night
Oh baby that was quite a punch,
YES
could somebody check my pulse?
-my pulse
It's been a minute since I tasted blood,
I forgot how good this was
-forgot how good this was
Oh honey it's a fucked up world,
can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BA
Somebody better hold me BAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done
thinking
through it!
'cause I got
Bruises
Doing
something
stupid
Oh honey it's a fucked up world,
you can bet your life on that
Somebody better hold me back
Doing
something
stupid
Anyway, here's one more double
Doing
something
stupid
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done
thinking
through it!
'cause I got
Bruises
Doing
something
stupid
Oh honey it's a fucked up world,
can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
Invaders must die
Doing
something
stupid
Invaders must die
Doing
something
stupid
Oh baby that was quite a punch,
could somebody check my pulse?
It's been a minute since I tasted blood,
I forgot how good this was
Oh honey it's a fucked up world,
can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BA
Somebody better hold me BAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
Invaders must die
Subtitle might be inaccurate for this part
They will never know
What i got for show
Imma sell my soul
I dont really care for what you know
You could see in my eyes and all
My brand new chain wide, yo
I'm the realest and I came with the dough
I dont really care for what you know
They will never know
What i got for show
Imma sell my soul
I dont really care for what you know
You could see it in my eyes and all
My brand new chain wide, yo
I'm the realest and I came with the dough
I dont really care for what you know
They will never know
What i got for show
Imma sell my soul
I dont really care for what you know
You could see it in my eyes and all
My brand new chain wide, yo
I'm the realest and I came with the dough
I dont really care for what you know
They will never know
What i got for show
You could see it in my eyes and all
My brand new chain wide, yo
They will never know
What i got for show
You could see it in my eyes and all
My brand new chain wide, yo
In the party, tryna disconnect
Out of body, in my element
Nearly flyin', ready to transcend
Then I hear my phone ring and it's you again
Complainin', so restrainin'
Won't you loosen your grip?
Need space here, solo ravin'
Give me less of your lip and pace it
Cool it with the statements
Cool it with the sensitive, but no
I still hear the tone
You must be out of your mind
Blowing me up on my Phoneline
(Why you blowing up my Phoneline)
Call me and I'ma decline
(I'm gon' decline)
And I'm gon' get back in my own time
Won't lie, I'm about to leave you on silent
My head goes, yeah, I feel it start
I got lights in my soul, shade in my heart
I'm about to leave you on silent
This ain't me, but it's close, that's my favorite part
(Why you blowing up my Phoneline)
It's all good, grab a cup and get your stupid on
Well the times, they change, and we remain
(Call me and I'ma decline)
​the same we always were
(And I'm gon' get back in my own time)
And if you're tired again, ignore the pain
(Won't lie)
​and smile-
I'm about to leave you on silent
And I don't wanna waste your time
Just tryna make you understand
Yeah, maybe I'm a broken man
But I still work
No, I don't wanna waste your time
Just tryna make you understand
Yeah, maybe I'm a broken man
But I still work
Last one
-work
NEIIIII
NOOOOOOOO
*Sounds of disagreement*
Feel free to hate me
NOO
I don't want a lot for Christmas
*VINE BOOM*
I don't want a non for Christmas
NOO
Yes, Yes, Yes
There is just one thing I need
Oh, just- just get the *inaudible*
I don't care about the PUSSY
ŭ̸̘̠n̷̞̠͋̈d̶̻̋̂e̴̛̟r̸͇̈́̓ǹ̷̡̠ë̵̡̫̃ȃ̴̢t̷̜͆̓h̷̨̿ ̸̣̩̓t̷̰͝ẖ̴̢͒͠e̷͊̋͜ ̷̭͓̽̑c̴̠͚̒ḧ̷̟́ȓ̵̙͝i̶̡͉̽s̸͂ͅt̶͖̍m̷̙̥̋͛a̷̱̣͝s̵̱̭̽̃ ̴͓̖͗ṭ̶͇̈́́r̶̹̻̊ḙ̸͒e̸̠͋̊
I just want you for my own
MY HIP TRACKER TURNED OFF
More than you could eva know
*inaudible* -my hip tracker was off?!
Make my wis come true
Oh my god
All I want for CURISUMAS is you
All I WaNt fOr CurIsuMas iS You
aLL I wANt fOr CuRiSUmaS Is yOu
alL i waNT FoR CuRisuMAs Is YOu
All I WaNt fOr CurIsuMas iS You
aLL I wANt fOr CuRiSUmaS Is yOu
alL i waNT FoR CuRisuMAs Is YOu
All I WaNt fOr CurIsuMas iS You
aLL I wANt fOr CuRiSUmaS Is yOu
alL i waNT FoR CuRisuMAs Is YOu
All I WaNt fOr CurIsuMas iS You
aLL I wANt fOr CuRiSUmaS Is yOu
alL i waNT FoR CuRisuMAs Is YOu
All I WaNt fOr CurIsuMas iS You
aLL I wANt fOr CuRiSUmaS Is yOu
All I want for CURISUMAS is you
*Gamecube*
EUH HA HA
OH NOO
*SIREN*
I don't want a lot for Christmas
*laughing*
There is just one thing I need
Hell yeah
*laughing continues*
Don't care about the presents underneath the Christmas tree
Look up "Explorers of the Internet" if you would like to know more
I don't need to hang my stocking there upon the fireplace
Explorers of the Internet
DROP
Santa Claus won't make me happy with a toy on Christmas Day
*Still laughing*
I just want DEEZ NUTZ GOTTEM
More a- ᵃ- a- a-
Make my wish come true
Make my wish come ᵗʳᵘᵉ
All I want for Christmas is you
Cock and-
You
Ouy
Lol
You
I'm just gonna keep on waiting underneath the mistletoe
w̶̱̑͂ä̷͚͔́̕ȋ̵̤ẗ̵̲́̉i̶̢̐n̵͖͝g̵̛̲ ̵̫̿̆ŭ̵́͜n̶̹̬̔͘d̷͙̀e̶̘̹̔r̴̯͑̎ǹ̸̢͜e̷͙͝ạ̴̓t̴̨̫͒͘ḣ̷̛̹̣ ̸͔̠́t̸̥̳̀ḥ̴̛̐e̴̫͒̔ ̶̮̺͒̒m̷̪͘i̸̘̝͌s̸̼̍t̴͕̤́͘l̶̗͊͗e̵̯̮͌̃t̵̛̖̓ö̴̠́͝è̶̢̹̅
❗👀❗
I've listened to this so many times
I̸̭̔͊ ̵̧̿̑̚w̴͚̖̿̿̆ó̸̡̰͚̆́n̷͎͓̍̑'̵̩͊͘͝t̶̝̠̓͆̈́ ̸̻̑m̴̻̀a̶̭͕̞͑̌̔k̸̟̳͗͂͂e̸̺̖͌ ̷̫̐a̷̭̣̔ ̷̥̤͓̓͋l̸̥̳̈́̈́͘i̵͍͗ś̵̙̱̏͘t̴̩̅͠ ̷̘͓̩̽̈a̶̭̦͐̌͐n̶̼̾̎̃ď̸̮̺͠ ̸̦̼̀̽̈́͜s̷̬̻̹̎̍̚e̷͕̮̘̋n̵̦͝d̴͙̅͗̏ ̸̣̭̿͂̌i̴̞̍̌ͅt̶̤͑̈̈́ ̷̡͋̏̌t̸͚̹̠̓̈́͝o̶̮͑ ̷̪͍͗͝ț̶̠͋h̸͖̀͠é̸͈͇͂͠ ̶̢̠̝̆͝N̷̐̒ͅo̶̜̤͔̅́̈́ŗ̴̃͘͘t̴̼͈̾̐͆h̶̜̅͛̚ ̷̤̙̀́P̶̭̹͕̀o̶̜͍̊l̴̦̰̟̈̀̐e̴̘̳̹̓͆͘ ̸͔̱̻͑͝͠f̶̝͎̈̇̊o̶̘̜͗͝r̶̡͋̆̑ ̸̦̠̃̈́͠Ș̸̨̥̾̈̕ā̶̠̣̈̋i̴̯͐ǹ̸̮͍t̴̜̲̓ ̵͓͔͌́N̴̺̤̥̉ĭ̴̫̼̆c̵̢̾͒̚k̷̮̪̓͑͗
that I've love- I've learned to love it
I̸̢̲͗̑͝ ̵̫̰͍̈́̒̐w̷͇̺͔̍̓o̷̧͓̝̓n̶̥̋'̸̘̪͖̓̀͝ț̶͇́̿̂͜ ̷̪̫̽͌̒͜ȩ̵̤̀v̴̺̣̐͜ȩ̷͂̕n̸̨̅ ̷̻̩̉̚s̴̮̹̈́̊͠t̷͓̀ͅa̷͔̅y̸̠̔͝ ̸̻͜͝a̷̧̔w̵͓͊̏a̶̝̋̇̈ͅk̵̗̐̓ḙ̷̀̂͂ ̸̼̙̐t̷̨̻̝̽o̵̡̻̙͆͝ ̵͖͒h̶̹͛e̶̢̼̙̍͌͠ā̵̼̞͘r̷͎̯͎̿̚̕ ̸͉́̿t̵̫̀̈͜h̷̞̱̄ͅo̸̙͛̿͝s̴͔͋̐͆è̵̡͑̈͜-̴̯̍͘
I won't even stay awake to hear those-
I just want you here tonight
Holding on to me so tight
Holy Shit
What more can I do?
Oh, baby, all I want for Christmas is you
YOᵁOUᴼᵁOU
ᴼʰ-oh, all the lights are shining so brightly everywhere
And the sound of children's laughter fills the air
*ALARM*
And everyone is singing
I hear those sleigh bells ringing
I cannot understand what you're saying
Santa, won't you bring me the one I really need?
Won't you please bring my baby to me?
I don't want a lot for Christmas
This is all I'm asking for
FUCK *;LL;:;*
I just wanna see my baby standing right outside my door
Oh my-
This is what I get
I just wanna see my baby standing right outside my door
BRRRR
I just want you for my own
More than you could ever know
ඞ
*REVERSE FART*
Make my wish come true
Christmas- there we go
Oh, baby, all I want for Christmas is you
YouuuUUUUᵁᵁᵁᵁᵁ
*Mii Channel Theme*
Hip tracker, there we go
Ohh my god
ᵁᵁᵁᵁᵁᵁᵁᵁᵁᴵᵁᴵᴵᴵᴵ
*Clapping*
Thank you, thank you all
I hope you enjoyed
*VINE BOOM*
I hope it's been worth the wait
After- After 9 years
Hopefully It's been worth the wait
Subtitles - MitchSirco
*despair*
I hate you, thank you
It's okay, you're allowed to hate me
You're allowed to hate me
You're never forgiven
You're never-