Lost on a moonlit night
Summer, one-nine
Thought it would last forever
Never felt more alive
Life was so simple then
A perpetual high
Those days that I knew may be gone
But I won't let them die
Time's a thief that keeps on stealing
I just keep on chasing that feeling
Won't give up, won't stop beliving
I just keep on chasing, chasing that
Feeling
Chasing that feeling
It's all I know, it's all I know
Didn't know what I had, did I?
Left it all in the past
Hoping for twice in a lifetime
Is that too much to ask?
Lightning across the sky
Went by in a flash
I'll keep running faster
Chasing one more chance
Time's a thief that keeps on stealing
I just keep on chasing that feeling
Won't give up, won't stop beliving
I just keep on chasing, chasing that
Feeling
Chasing that feeling
It's all I know, it's all I know
I'm chasing
Chasing
In my kaleidoscopе
Are pressed butterflies
Reminding me I've only one life
(One life)
(One life, one life)
Time's a thief that keeps on stealing
I just keep on chasing that feeling
Won't give up, won't stop beliving
I just keep on chasing, chasing that
Feeling
Chasing that feeling
It's all I know, it's all I know
know
I keep chasing, chasing
I'm chasing
Chasing
I'm chasing my feeling
Subtitles by @MitchSirco