Will you decide to stay
When the accents fade away
'Cause you're a busy boy
And I'm not too sure
If I can fit in your schedule
You're from the other side of town
Where the world is upside down
Ah
Yeah
It doesn't matter much to me
'Cause everything you are
Is all I wanna be
If I took the plane would you remember me
I'm in love with a fox boy on the internet
Sounds weird but it's true
No, I won't give up
No, I won't give up on you
I'm in love with a fox boy on the internet
Sounds weird but it's you
And I don't even know your name
I don't even know your name
You're looking happier 👏👏
In every selfie with your friend
You're such a busy boy, but I am sure
I can give you what he gives you
So if you've had a bad day
I'm only a Telegram message away
Ah yeah
Baby you matter much to me
'Cause everything you are
Is all I wanna be
If I took the plane, would you remember me?
I'm in love with a fox boy on the internet
Sounds weird but it's true
No, I won't give up
No, I won't give up on you
I'm in love with a fox boy on the internet
Sounds weird but it's you
Ah yeah
And I don't even know your name
I don't even know your name
(You're so far away, so far away)
(Could I have made you stay?)
(Now I'm the one who pays)
You're so far away, so far away
Could I have made you stay?
Now I'm the one who pays
You're so far away, so far away
Could I have made you stay?
Now I'm the one who pays
You're so far away, so far away
Could I have made you stay?
Now I'm the one who pays
I'm in love with a fox boy on the internet
Sounds weird but it's true
No, I won't give up
No, I won't give up on you
I'm in love with a fox boy on the internet
Sounds weird but it's you
I don't even know your name
(So far away)
Subtitles - MitchSirco