Oh, we've been doin' this since dark ages,
with fast paces
Takin' rock and metal,
throwin' Drum and Bass in
This one goes out to the cell dwellers
Who stood alone,
metronome full force to the trendsetters
Rock the people,
rush the stage
Keeping bodies movin', yeah, but
melting the face
Crushin' the metal,
punchin' the bass
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKEOVER!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Haha,
rush the stage
Get ready, motherfucker!
Brace for takeover!
Brace for Takeover!
Brace for TAkeover!
Brace for TAKeover!
Brace for TAKEover!
Brace for TAKEOver!
Brace for TAKEOVer!
Brace for TAKEOVEr!
Brace for TAKEOVER!
Will we make it out alive?
Huh!
Yeah!
Haha
You better be ready, yeah
Brace for takeover!
Watch how we break it out
Rockin' the place as you
Brace for takeover!
Watch how we tear it out
Haha, you see,
The Qemists are the players,
Z's the controller
This ain't a game, yeah
Q set the tone,
Zardonic the reloader
Getting so heavy, yeah, you
Crushin' the metal,
punchin' the bass
Rockin' the place as you brace for takeover!
Rockin' the place as you brace for Takeover!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAkeover!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKeover!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKEover!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKEOver!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKEOVer!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKEOVEr!
Rockin' the place as you brace for TAKEOVER!
Will we make it out alive?
:3
Oh baby, that was quite a punch
Could somebody check my pulse?
It's been a minute since I tasted blood
I forgot how good this was
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
Can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BA
Somebody better hold me BAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
You can bet your life on that
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BA
Somebody better hold me BAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAACK
My god!
Just do it!
I'm so done thinking through it!
'Cause I got
Bruises
Doing something stupid
Oh honey, it's a fucked up world
Can't you see the fun in that?
Somebody better hold me
Somebody better hold me BAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAA
Somebody better hold me BAAAAAAACK
Last night took an L,
but tonight I bounce back
Wake up every morning,
by the night, I count stacks
Knew that ass was real
when I hit, it bounce back
(Bounce back)
(You ain't getting checks) (short, short, short, short)
Last night took an L,
but tonight I bounce back
Boy, I been broke as hell,
cashed a check and bounced back
D town LAX,
every week I bounce back
If you a real one,
then you know how to bounce back
Don't owe nobody, owe nobody
Always on the fuckin' job,
I got no hobbies
Got the city fuckin' with me
cause I'm homegrown
Vibin' out more than my phone
Though leave me 'lone,
me on my own though
Look, I cut that bitch off like an edit
My daddy a G, it's genetics
(Straight up)
I heard ya new shit, it's pathetic
(Damn)
Ya contract should be s-shredded
Took my dogs on a private jet from the public housing
I kept it G, yeah, one thousand
Clique star studded like the Paramount mountain
Everything I do is righteous
Betting on me is the right risk
Even in a fucking crisis
I'm never on some switching sides shit
I switch gears to the night shift
Blacking out cause I'm enlightened
God talk to me in silence
But I hear him every time mane
(Thank you God, God bless you, thank you so much)
Last night took an L,
but tonight I bounce back
Wake up every morning,
by the night, I count stacks
Knew that ass was real
when I hit, it bounce back
(Bounce back)
(You ain't getting checks) (short, short, short, short)
Last night took an L,
but tonight I bounce back
Boy, I been broke as hell,
cashed a check and bounced back
D town LAX,
every week I bounce back
If you a real one,
then you know how to bounce back
Lookin' for Ms like I lost a friend
Jump out of my bed like, "Where the bread"
You gon' hold a egg, waiter bring the check
When we talk, we Kalashnikov,
keep us in your thoughts
Fully dressed at the crack of dawn,
weapons letting off
I can hear them from the block
see them creeping through the fog
Season's greetings,
now feeding season can start, oh my God
Look alive,
lookin' like I live life on the crooked line
Doin' fine,
you want maximum stupid, I am the guy
First of all,
fuck the fuckin' law, we is fuckin' raw
Steak tartare,
oysters on the half-shell, sushi bar
Life a bitch,
and the pussy fish, still fucked her raw
I'm a dog,
I'm a dirty dog, ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
Ol' Dirty Bastard,
go in your jaw, shimmy, shimmy, ya
Got the semi in the hemi,
go and gimme, gimme, ya
Pugilistic, my linguistics are Jeru the Damaja
And I rap it pornographic,
bitch, set up the camera
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui (Ayy)
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui (Ah, oui oui)
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui (Mon cheri, mon cheri)
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui (Ah, oui oui)
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui
Ooh, la la, ah, oui oui (Mon cheri)
Sometimes when the going gets tough
You gotta look at your friends beside you
Every now and then, send a prayer up
Cause the devil's two steps behind you
And count your lucky stars
That trouble don't come and find you
So step into the ring brother
Crack another smile
There's only gonna be one standing
When I'm through
You walk the lonely road
But you'll be
But you'll be FII
But you'll be FIIIIII
But you'll be FIIIIIIIINE
Cause these bright lights are better than gold
I would never let go
Try hard to find my way
Through and through
This time doing better than you know
Nobody's gonna stop the show
Look what you made me do
free his mind at night,
at, at,
at night
DAY AND NIGHT
Day and Night
day and night
DAY AND NIGHT
Day and Night
day and night
Da-,  Da-,  Da-,  Da-,
DAY AND NIGHT
Day and Night
day and night
DAY AND NIGHT
Day and Night
day and night
Da-,  Da-,  Da-,  Da-,
So you thought that, apparently
This town just wasn't big enough, well
Now that makes two of us, so
Put em up and pray
*oh*
*aaaa*
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
*ohh*
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
*oh*
*aaaa*
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
*ohh*
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
*oh*
*aaaah*
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
*ohh*
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
'Cause you got me howlin'
*oh*
*aaaah*
Even if my jokes aren't funny
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
My tongue tied up, honey
*ohh*
*aaaaaah*
And I don't need to speak a single word
*ehh*
*aaaaaah*
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
'Cause you got me howlin'
Even if I lost all my money
This river runs deep, honey
And I don't need to speak a single word
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
awoooo
Even if my jokes aren't funny
My tongue tied up, honey
And I don't need to speak a single word
'Cause you got me howlin'
Um, eh, ah,
play me like a bass guitar
Simmer down and mess me up
Trippin' like I'm Jimmy at Woodstock
Um, eh, ah,
drive me round in your red Ford
Shivers down my spinal cord
Oh-oh-oh, oh-oh,
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
Even if I lost all my money
This river runs deep, honey
And I don't need to speak a single word
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
Even if my jokes aren't funny
My tongue tied up, honey
And I don't need to speak a single word
Cause you got me howlin'
Cause you got me 🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
Cause you got me 🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
'Cause you got me howlin'
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
Even if I lost all my money
This river runs deep, honey
And I don't need to speak a single word
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
Even if my jokes aren't funny
My tongue tied up, honey
And I don't need to speak a single word
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
🦴
🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
'Cause you got me howlin', howlin'
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴🦴
Style too dangerous
Flow too murderous
Beats too treacherous
You can't handle this
Mic technician, here me heat it up so feel the friction
Obliterate when I disintegrate the competition
You know how we do to blow it back
Yo, thats our only mission
Its ringing from the bang
The flash distorts your vision
Cold flows so frigid, I'm wizard or mic magician
Camo & Krooked on the beat
and they the bomb technicians
Peep the precision of this collaborative composition
In addition, witness the the damage that's done
Its about to blow UP
None other than the illest
Illest
We set it off
WE SET IT OFF
🪑➡️➡️➡️➡️
🪑➡️➡️➡️➡️↩️
⬅️⬅️⬅️⬅️🪑
↪️⬅️⬅️⬅️⬅️​​🪑
None other than the illest
Illest
🪑➡️➡️➡️➡️
🪑➡️➡️➡️➡️↩️
Na-Na-Na Na-Na-Na
Solo Killa
None other than the illest
Illest
So cold, my heavyweight soul
So weighed down by the things that I know
All told I got too bold
Space wizards, hollywood blizzards
Cheatin’ at cards with illuminati lizards
From Indiana out to Valhalla
They know my name
‘cause nobody does it better, yea
And it’s strange but I don’t mind
I drive off the edge of the earth to kill time
The storm’s comin’
You better get runnin’
Wherever I am I’m starting up something
I reckon in 21 seconds
I’m about to blow this thing straight to the heavens
Still stressin’, Still second guessing
Paid my price but learned no lesson
*YEA*
So cold, my heavyweight soul
So weighed down by the things that I know
All told I got too bold, Heart of Gold?
No, I do it like that
like that
I do it like that
I'll take you with me wherever I go
I'll keep you company, but what do I know?
You take no bullet for me, but I know
And I still care
Emotionally confused, that feeling is slapped in my views
and I got used and now I don't know who to trust
My heart went so cold, because of lies that I was told
now I'm alone, I don't remembеr how to love
Blaming all my flaws on you, when I should have supportеd you
and now I realize I’ve never done enough
Behind doors going crazy, letting inside me is satan
you sedate me when I hear you say:
I'll take you with me wherever I go
I'll keep you company, but what do I know?
You take no bullet for me, but I know
And I still care
All your friends they judge me, asking why you even love me
they don't understand or rather see my pain
Blinded by the lights and all the celebrity gossip
got me treating relationships like a game
Staring in the mirror, I see nothing hasn't changed
while everybody seems to think I ain't the same
All I hear is voices saying:
"You take no bullet for me"
I hear them loads
Voices I hear them throw the type of words
that take control of your body, mind and your soul
Choking on your ego, deusa gold is rolled,
is what they say knowing you go
Now they got you on your own
Diseased is what this game is, pokerface you're about to fold
That's just the lies that you were told, the story never gets old
You was young wise en was bold
Now you faded and life is cold, it’s got me not answering the phone
and I’m too scared to get you involved
Ey, blue sky tide help me clear my mind
Full of nothing I need, no
(no)
I look up sometimes and to my surprise
I can finally breathe, woah
(woah)
It's a real thin line 'tween wasting time
And getting some peace though
(though)
All the depths I dive try to finally find out
What it all means
OH FAITHFUL
INNER DEMONS
GIVE ME SOMETHING
TO BELIEVE IN
I'VE BEEN
Yeah,
Yeah, ether
(Ethеr)
Oh faithful
Inner demons
Give me something
to believe in
I've been stumbling
'round the ether
I keep wondering
why I'm here
Subtitles might be inaccruate for this part soz
Go on, let me then, take you for a foolin'
I jump for that steel tool
I jump for the key
Bless the land, my posture feed that
When you're alone
When you’re steady in the long wind, don't need to worry
Inna go then, when I lie about them, they’re gonna be free
Aye, blood, don’t tell fake, hyper socials, you clickbait
Money in real life, but mine didn't matter how I feel like, boy
Man, they give me bloodclaat, what am I saying
Say anything and you're doomed with my dick
Anything you talk, we definite
Hit it like this, life can't lie anytime
Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah, Yeah
Yeah,
Yeah, ether
Subtitles might be inaccruate for this part too soz
Come, Corey, can you talk to me
can some white guy start at me
Did you just do crime properly
Selfish, a bad mind, let's fuck, Corey
Eat my Nina, this thing so no boy
could ever try so near to me
But man in a list, sing your boss up,
bitches wanna rip off your artery
So let's get gassed, hold some more Henny inside us
We can, you wanna see violence,
I'm blaming this on my ignorance
Living off a seaside ting, prison's a job,
can't ever let 'em win
Beats of love are vulgar, so keep the music,
hope it all screams
Force fields,
mind cracks
Where we're going we won't be coming back
Into the void,
splintershock
Nobody can hear you when you're in the dark
Lifeline,
feeble glow
Feel the hunger of what lurks below
A pale flash,
the simple truth
You aren't even sure what you've got left to prove
Splintershock
Baby puttin' on for the city
Baby, he the realest, Baby prolly got a couple million
Baby hang with four or five killers
Baby got children, Baby prolly still drug dealin'
Baby ain't a trapper, he a rapper
Baby makin' classics, Baby in the hood gettin' active
Baby keep it real with his people
Baby like a preacher
Baby puttin' on for the city
Baby, he the realest, Baby prolly got a couple million
Baby hang with four or five killers
Baby got children, Baby prolly still drug dealin'
Baby ain't a trapper, he a rapper
Baby makin' classics, Baby in the hood gettin' active
Baby keep it real with his people, Baby like a preacher
Baby prolly still sell reefer
Baby puttin' on for the city
Baby, he the realest, Baby prolly got a couple million
Baby keep it real with his people
Baby like a preacher, Baby prolly still sell reefer
Baby puttin' on for the city
Baby, he the realest, Baby prolly got a couple million
Leave it all behind
Baby hang with four or five killers
Baby got children, Baby prolly still drug dealin'
Baby ain't a trapper, he a rapper
Baby puttin' on for the city
Baby, he the realest, Baby prolly got a couple million
Baby keep it real with his people
Baby like a preacher, Baby prolly still sell reefer
Baby puttin' on for the city
Baby, he the realest, Baby prolly got a couple million
Baby hang with four or five killers
Baby got children, Baby prolly still drug dealin'
Baby ain't a trapper, he a rapper
Baby makin' classics,
Leave it all behind
Read between the lines
Don't forget this moment
It is your life
As I walk through the battle
The ashes lead the way
No fire cast upon me
Shall quell the light you gave
Comrades march in mourning
But we stand not afraid
A warrior hath fallen
With legacy in wake
I stare through the abyss
I'm hearing your voice,
echo all that you left with me
As I stare through the abyss
I follow your voice
to the depths
'til my shadows
rest in peace
Peace
As I stare through the abyss
I follow your voice
to the depths
'til my shadows
rest in peace
I stare through the abyss
I'm hearing your voice,
echo all that you left with me
As I stare through the abyss
I follow your voice
to the depths
'til my shadows
rest in peace
A lucky, lucky girl
She got married to a boy like you
She'd kick you out if she ever, ever knew
'Bout all the - you tell me that you do
*telegram ping*
Dirty, dirty boy
You know everyone is talking on the scene
I hear them whispering 'bout the places that you've been
And how you don't know how to keep your business clean
Mummy don't know daddy's getting hot
At the body shop, doing something unholy
He's sat back while she's dropping it,
she be popping it
Yeah, she put it down slowly
Oh-ee-oh-ee-oh, he left his kids at
Ho-ee-oh-ee-ome, so he can get that
Mummy don't know daddy's getting hot
At the body shop, doing something unholy
I know I'm fine
But the money makes me handsomer
Walk around, smelling like a come-up in the answer for her problems
but I'm not him, I don't mind it though
You don't like me how you think you do, I like it though
I know I'm fine
But the money makes me handsomer
Walk around, smelling like a come-up in the answer for her problems
but I'm not him, I don't mind it though
You don't like me how you think you do, I like it though
All religion,
supersonic
My existence,
you can't resist us
Can't resist us
Supersonic
Did the math, I'm baby Johnny Cash
My girl gon' throw it back
Damn, my life is Cinemax
Holly hell, this smacks
I make hits and you make trash
I'm on vacay do not ask
Poolside eating apple jacks
Shut up bitch
(shut up)
Big deal like Tj Maxx
(Maxx)
Pop some cataracts
Watching Art Attack
(woo)
Nick Cage, how I act
Heavily dislike tax
Got some Asics on my feet, never wear Air Max
I'm in the cut, like a wound
Wake yo' ass up, make some room
In my girl coming soon
I don't fuck with honeymoons
Throw some money on my tomb
Finesse too hard, I'm feeling oom
Girls love me, they wanna spoon
Let me finish, I'll resume
Flame suit, french leather and my girl bad
Gatekeeper say it's open, I ain't calling back
15 minute TED Talk, collecting 40 racks
One milly paid in tax, bitch do the math
Do the math, bitch, do the math
When I'm falling down
Will you pick me up again?
When I'm too far gone
Dead in the eyes of my friends
Will you take me out of here
When I'm staring down the barrel
When I'm blinded by the lights
When I cannot see your face?
Take me out of here
All I believe
And all I've known
Are being taken from me
Can't get home
Yeah, do your worst
When worlds collide
Let their fear collapse
Bring no surprise
Take me out of here
Feed the fire,
break your vision
Throw your fists up
come with me
Feed the fire,
break your vision
Throw your fists up
come with me
Feed the fire,
break your vision
Throw your fists up
come with me
Feed the fire,
break your vision
Throw your fists up
come with me
And we fall with you
And we fall
And we fa- a- a- a- a- a- a- a- a-
And we fall with you
And we fall
So listen up, keep your ears to the ground
Don't go getting mistaken now
I'm the dude with the don't care crown
And I ain't gonna be taken down
I ain't lettin' my spirits down
'Cause ain't much matter that much I found
I'm the dude with the don't care crown
And I ain't gonna be taken down
I ain't gonna be taken down
Alright, alright, worry keeps you up all night
Could just be a problem with the things you keep inside your mind
I get that it's hard to find recipes for living right
Maybe take a seat, and I'll tell you how it goes
(yeah)
We can never know everything, everything
So I've been letting go everything, everything
Relax and then rejoice, 'cause you can't change a thing
Disappointment is a choice, that's the thing, that's the thing
that's the thing, that's the thing
So listen up, keep your ears to the ground
Don't go getting mistaken now
I'm the dude with the don't care crown
And I ain't gonna be taken down
I ain't lettin' my spirits down
'Cause ain't much matter that much I found
I'm the dude with the don't care crown
And I ain't gonna be taken down
I ain't gonna be taken down
So choose something to believe in
You know we give life it's meaning, oh
If I search my feelings, I don't know
And it's beyond comprehension
You know I don't sense the tension, oh
In place of redemption, I let go
And well, I spent so much time with the don't care crown
That I don't care how it's been weighing me down
And I can't be open in my heart now
I'm feeling nothing at all
I ain't lettin' my spirits down
'Cause ain't much matter that much I found
I'm the dude with the don't care crown
And I ain't gonna be taken down
And I ain't gonna be taken DOWN
Don't go getting mistaken now
DOWN
I ain't gonna be taken down
'Cause ain't much matter that much I found
And I ain't gonna be taken down
I keep holdin' on
Broken footsteps on the floor
Pick myself up and carry on
'Cause something's waiting for me
And I won't let them ride my soul
I keep holdin' on
Keep my direction and soon I'll be turned to gold
(turned to gold)
I'm a king without a throne
A heart without a home
Just cards that I've been dealt in life
I walk the road alone
But my hope will never die
(my hope will never die)
MOM GET THE CAMERA
OH MY GOD
OOHOHOOHH
Two step, then I bring it right back
But my hope will never di-
One step, now take it right back
Two step, then I bring it right back
I keep holding on
One step, now take it right back
Two step, then I bring it right back
But my hope will never di-
One step, now take it right back
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
step with it, no limit
One step, now take it right back
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
When you see me in the club, the party on lock
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
step with it, no limit
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
When you see me in the club, the party on lock
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
step with it, no limit
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
When you see me in the club, the party on lock
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
step with it, no limit
When I step into the-
Ayy, ayy, ayy, ayy
From the bottom to the-
When you see me in the club (yeah, yeah, yeah)
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop (yeah, yeah, yeah)
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot (ayy, ayy,
ayy)
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top (yeah, yeah, yeah)
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
step with it, no limit
When I step into the club
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't s-
Drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
When you see me in the club, the party on lock
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
When I step into the club, drop it like it's hot
DJ turn it up from the bottom to the top
You've got to move with it,
step with it,
step with it, no limit
When I step into the-
From the bottom to the-
DJ turn it up, rock your body, don't stop
When I step into the-
And then a thin layer of fog comes in around my ankles
Roadies, that means dry ice,
we're gonna talk about this later
In the ancient time
An artist lead the way
But no one
Seem to underSTAAAAND
Chimes, Freddy?
In his heart he knew
The artist must be true
But the legend
of the rent
was way past due
And then Katie you come in with the bass
Come in with the bass
Shi-gu-di-gu-di-gu-di-ga
rim-bim-bim-bim-bim-bim-bim-bim-be-du-du-be-du-du-be-du
You're not hardcore
Unless you live hardcore
Will you not hard-
No, you're not hardcore-
Unless, you live hardc-
Unless, you live hardcore
The Legend of the rent was way past due
*dawwww*
Shi-gu-di-gu-di-gu-di-ga
Come in with the bass
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Feelin' like a polar bear burnin'
What are we gonna do?
I'm that fake smile gleamin'
Yeah, I'm the lie that you choose to believe in
Guess the truth kinda lost all meanin'
And I'm enjoying the view
Well I've been a lovin' lover
I've been a trusting brother
I'm taking my time to recover
And pickin' it up when I'm better
Oh, there's so much to see in a lifetime
So why does it feel like it flies by?
She's staring me down with the bright eyes
Don't threaten me with a good time
(Don't threaten me with a good time)
(-na na na na)
(Na na-na-na na na na na)
Na na-na-na na na na na
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Na na-na-na na na na na
Feelin' like a freight train runnin'
I'm that hurricane turnin'
Feelin' like a polar bear burnin'
What are we gonna do?
I'm that fake smile gleamin'
Yeah, I'm the lie that you choose to believe in
Guess the truth kinda lost all meanin'
And I'm enjoying the view
Oooh if we ever get out of here
Without making a sound
I've been fuckin' hoes and poppin' pillies
Man, I feel just like a rockstar
All my brothers got that gas
And they always be smokin' like a Rasta
Fuckin' with me, call up on a Uzi
And show up, man, them the shottas
When my homies pull up on your block
They make that thing go grah-ta-ta-ta
ayy, ayy
Switch my whip, came back in black
I'm startin' sayin', "Rest in peace to Bon Scott"
ayy
Close that door, we blowin' smoke
She ask me light a fire like I'm Morrison
Oooh if we ever get out of here
Act a fool on stage
Prolly leave my fuckin' show in a cop car
Ayy
Shit was legendary
Threw a TV out the window of the Montage
Without making a sound
Cocaine on the table, liquor pourin'
Don't give a damn, dude, your girlfriend is a groupie
She just tryna get in
Sayin', "I'm with the band"
Ayy, ayy
Now she actin' outta pocket
Tryna grab up on my pants, hundred bitches in my trailer
Say they ain't got a man
And they all brought a friend
Yeah, ayy
Oooh if we ever get out of here
I've been fuckin' hoes and poppin' pillies
Man, I feel just like a rockstar
All my brothers got that gas
And they always be smokin' like a Rasta
Fuckin' with me, call up on a Uzi
And show up, man, them the shottas
When my homies pull up on your block
They make that thing go grah-ta-ta-ta
I know that we fight like hell
But if I lose you feel I lose myself
I know there′s no way to win
(No way to win)
But I know I gotta walk away
I know that I cannot stay
So the healing can begin
I said I tried to fight it
And you tried to hide who you really were
And baby oh that hurt
And I did my best to make it better babe
But the love you couldn't give made it worse
But inside I′m slowly dying
Tryna push through all your lying
Tryna get what you won't give to me
(I just want your love)
I'm tryna push us higher
But now babe I′m gettin tired
Cuz you keep tryna clip my wings
Baby oh that hurt
But I still can′t separate
I still can't get away
From you
Oh, From you
But I know if I choose to stay
Oh baby you′ll just keep on taking till I'm through
Oh till I′m through
You must be out of your mind
Blowing me up on my Phoneline
(Why you blowing up my Phoneline)
Call me and I'ma decline
(I'm gon' decline)
And I'm gon' get back in my own time
Won't lie, I'm about to leave you on silent
I know that we fight like hell
But if I lose you feel I lose myself
I know there′s no way to win
(No way to win)
But I know I gotta walk away
I know that I cannot stay
So the healing can begin
I said I tried to fight it
And you tried to hide who you really were
And baby oh that hurt
And I did my best to make it better babe
But the love you couldn't give made it worse
V🅰️LUE$🅾️FT
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me mashin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me blaggin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me mashin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me blaggin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
FUCKING GOLD DUST
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me mashin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
It's like gold dust
You hear me coming through your speakers
You see me blaggin' up your airwaves
I know you can't get enough of my sound
*YEEEAA*
*huh huh huh*
*huh hᵤh hᵤh*
Thinking about you when I close my eyes
Like watching the stars across the night collide
And all the space between us two subside
So we stay awake until we see the sunrise
You take the light from the sky,
it fades when you're gone
But when you come back,
it shines on me like the dawn
Okay, okay, okay, let's go
Ooh, watching wild skies
Wishing with closed eyes
Ooh, run for a lifetime
Follow the signs
I put my pictures down
They're not as good as the real thing
"I wish I could go home"
You're just nostalgic
What do we wander from and only notice it now?
So be here with me
And I watched the water unfold
It's a feeling I want you to know
'Cause I'm not the same as I was
As I shoulder the weight of the world
I was setting in stone until I noticed it right
Do you see how you've grown?
Don't be sorry, then
And I fall from my bones
And now I know I'm alive
I want you to find it
And I watched the water unfold
It's a feeling I want you to know
'Cause I'm not the same as I was
As I shoulder the weight of the world
Thaw your hands now
(What I have become)
Put color in your cheeks
(Where I belong)
I missed you back then
So be here with me
here
with
me
here
with
me
And I watched the water unfold
It's a feeling I want you to know
know
And I watched the water unfold
It's a feeling I want you to know
'Cause I'm not the same as I was
As I shoulder the weight of the world
And I watched the water unfold
It's a feeling I want you to know
'Cause I'm not the same as I was
As I shoulder the weight of the world
And I watched the water unfold
It's a feeling I want you to know
'Cause I'm not the same as I was
As I shoulder the weight of the world
:)
Subtitles made by: @MitchSirco