I've been nerding out on the Goo 2.0 Shader
for the past like 3 months
And you can get it right now, on the Patreon
And get access to all the new stuff
We got all the new boring stuff
Like the new UI
More texture slots
LTCGI
SPS
And you got the really fucking cool nerdy shit too
You got, like the fucking mask channels
You got the UV Buses, right? But what are those?
Mask Channels, but like a global masking system
on fucking steroids
Right? You can say: "Okay, I want a texture mask"
"I want a capsule mask"
"I want a rim mask"
"I want a scrolling mask"
"I want your fucking mom's mask", right?
Cause, look at this shit, fucking
The drip is a different thing, 'cause we
masked the drip to have an emission, right?
And then the fucking-
We have a fucking rim mask
FUCKING HIP TRACK-
And the UV Busses, are like a way of saying:
"Okay, I want these UV's to be
like world space", right? Okay, cool
The fuck is going on
"Okay, now I want them to be
distorted with this texture", right?
That we can pan, and like-
And then, oh my God, I have
so many different things I wanna
do with all that, it's not even done yet
And so you should like get it
now to support me and all that shit
So I can fuck-
Oh yeah, everything is
documented too, so you can like
You see over there, you can
click the little question mark
And it'll tell you what it does
And so you're not like:
"Uh huh, yeah"
"What"
We don't have tutorials and shit right now
But, that's kinda the point, this is Early Access
After, the most of the stuff that I
wanna do for the shader is done
After we get tutorials
Then, it's gonna be released as a free update
Go get it now at Patreon
Fucking, patreon.shader.gay, lets go
Subtitles - MitchSirco