Just dropped in from the daydream
You know I always gotta cause a big scene
Gotta make everything about me
I've been like this since I was like thirteen
So let me bend your ears while I've got them
What is it you're really trying to run from
I guess that's the thing about problems
While you ignore them,
then you ain't got none
Oh, what a wonderful way to live
Cold, magnifying the things I did
I know something has got to give
I wait for the veil to lift
I'm feeling that choice in the way
I'm feeding that void every day
I'm screaming your voice in my brain
It's more than I can take
And oh
I'm feeling that choice in the way
A little blockade in my brain
Whatever comes next I pray
It isn't more than I can take, yeah
Always late to the party
So everybody might look upon me
Show them something better than I might be
Force feed a narrative, sell them what they wanna see
Wait
Maybe that's the way I put the walls up
No one ever gets to get a close up
That's the way illusions get bust up
Life's been a breeze so long as I've kept the front up
Hey, don't make me reflect on things
Avoiding it all is an easy win
No way can the loneliness settle in
It's my choice to pretend to be king
I'm feeling that choice in the way
I'm feeding that void every day
I'm screaming your voice in my brain
It's more than I can take
And oh
I'm feeling that choice in the way
A little blockade in my brain
Whatever comes next I pray
It isn't more than I can take, yeah
The person inside underwhelms me
So I pretend I'm something else entirely
A person who's better than me at everything
Rather you know that guy instead of me
It's funny how it took so long to realise
I thought I was alone at trying to live lies
Maybe everyone's a person being hid behind
Would we all be so alone if we empathised
Whoa, a depressing epiphany
I know you so far as you let me see
We're both different people way underneath
What happens when those people meet
I'm feeling that choice in the way
I'm feeding that void every day
I'm screaming your voice in my brain
It's more than I can take
And oh
I'm feeling that choice in the way
A little blockade in my brain
Whatever comes next I pray
It isn't more than I can take, yeah